<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial</id>
  <title>ngkoksongofficial TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-29T06:48:31+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/ngkoksongofficial.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from ngkoksongofficial</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272036493357534471</id>
    <title>Never a dull day during campaign season! At Tampines Round Market in the morning, I spoke about the importance of ensuring the Elected President is not beholden to any political party. We cannot have a President who may be manipulated to serve the politic</title>
    <updated>2023-08-27T16:15:42+00:00</updated>
    <content>Never a dull day during campaign season! At Tampines Round Market in the morning, I spoke about the importance of ensuring the Elected President is not beholden to any political party. We cannot have a President who may be manipulated to serve the political agenda of any party. By the time I got to Chinatown Complex around lunchtime, news had broken that another opposition party leader had endorsed one of the other candidates. Naturally, the media had many questions for me about this development. I shared my views frankly. Let's not mince words. The move by some members of opposition parties to endorse a certain candidate is dangerous and divisive. Turning the Presidential Election into a proxy for a General Election is a polarising move that aims to force Singaporeans to choose between a government-endorsed candidate and an opposition-endorsed candidate. I am glad that not all opposition parties have decided to do this. Responsible opposition politicians understand the difference between a PE and a GE. They know how important it is to ensure the President remains a unifying force in Singapore and not an office to be used as a backdoor to pressure the Government on policy matters. I was very happy to receive such a warm welcome from Singaporeans at both hawker centres. Many, many people came to say hello, including some who are still too young to vote but have been following the developments closely. Wonderful to see such political awareness among the future electorate. In the evening, I had a more lighthearted session with @Hao on a TikTok livestream where he invited his followers and friends to Ask Me Anything or AMA! We talked about a wide range of topics, including how to deal with personal conflicts, managing one's finances and why the President cannot lower the GST rate. Another AMA video which I had filmed together with Tharman also premiered on Straits Times. We both fielded questions on everything from mental health among youth to how we would celebrate if we won the election. Just a few days left before we go to the polls. I'm going all out to meet as many Singaporeans as I can.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272036493357534471" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-27T16:15:42+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272264036132130056</id>
    <title>I’ve always been serious when it comes to discharging my duties. At the same time, I am a very lighthearted person. In my 45 years of public service, I took my job of protecting our reserves seriously because I found joy in contributing to our growth. It </title>
    <updated>2023-08-28T06:58:39+00:00</updated>
    <content>I’ve always been serious when it comes to discharging my duties. At the same time, I am a very lighthearted person. In my 45 years of public service, I took my job of protecting our reserves seriously because I found joy in contributing to our growth. It was never a burden.  The past few weeks have been amazing. Meeting all of you has given me so much joy and I want to be seen as your friend in the Istana. But I will not give in to fear or favour when it comes to safeguarding our treasures. The president must ultimately have the competence and expertise to be the head of state.#ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272264036132130056" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-28T06:58:39+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272310875845840146</id>
    <title>I am not a yes-man. In my 45 years of public service, I had plenty of experience standing my ground to do what was right, even if that meant disagreeing with people I reported to. If I am elected as your President, I will not hesitate to object to decisio</title>
    <updated>2023-08-28T10:00:25+00:00</updated>
    <content>I am not a yes-man. In my 45 years of public service, I had plenty of experience standing my ground to do what was right, even if that meant disagreeing with people I reported to. If I am elected as your President, I will not hesitate to object to decisions that are against the interests of the people of Singapore. I know how to work with the Government, for the people of Singapore, without being disruptive. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272310875845840146" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-28T10:00:25+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272328184421567752</id>
    <title>Dear Singaporeans, we must not get confused between the Presidential Election and the General Election. Members of some opposition parties have banded together to show their support for one of the other candidates. Another candidate is endorsed by the gov</title>
    <updated>2023-08-28T11:07:35+00:00</updated>
    <content>Dear Singaporeans, we must not get confused between the Presidential Election and the General Election. Members of some opposition parties have banded together to show their support for one of the other candidates. Another candidate is endorsed by the governing party. We must not let them turn this into a proxy fight between the Government and the opposition. This election is not about that. It is about all the people of Singapore, regardless of political affiliations.  The President must be a unifying force, not another source of division and discord. Those who wish to fight it out in the political arena should wait for the next GE. Stand united with me in solidarity to uphold the integrity and honour of the President’s office. 🖐🏼❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272328184421567752" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-28T11:07:35+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272346659336555794</id>
    <title>I will not stand for politicians making a mockery out of our Presidency. Since independence, Singapore has been recognised internationally for its exceptional political and social stability. Our founding leaders and our past generations have worked hard i</title>
    <updated>2023-08-28T12:19:17+00:00</updated>
    <content>I will not stand for politicians making a mockery out of our Presidency. Since independence, Singapore has been recognised internationally for its exceptional political and social stability. Our founding leaders and our past generations have worked hard in unity to lift us out of poverty into a first-world country. It is critical now, more than ever, that our head of state is able to navigate Singapore through crises. The office must be respected and honoured. I stand as a non partisan candidate, not beholden to anyone. I will not be pressured by partisan interests. I want to serve the people of Singapore honourably. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272346659336555794" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-28T12:19:17+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272372802202766599</id>
    <title>Diversity is our strength. Don't let our differences divide us. Staying united is how we stay strong in the face of an uncertain future, and protecting that unity is a key role of the President. I want to be a President for all, a President who is not beh</title>
    <updated>2023-08-28T14:00:43+00:00</updated>
    <content>Diversity is our strength. Don't let our differences divide us. Staying united is how we stay strong in the face of an uncertain future, and protecting that unity is a key role of the President. I want to be a President for all, a President who is not beholden to any political agenda, to rally our people around our common goals and shared dreams. Please, don't let partisanship pollute the Presidency. Help me safeguard our social fabric. Vote for me 🖐🏼❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272372802202766599" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-28T14:00:43+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272384642949451015</id>
    <title>How can a candidate be independent if he is dependent on the support of opposition party leaders? Singaporeans are not so easily fooled. There is a real danger that he might be manipulated by political parties serving their own interests if elected. He ev</title>
    <updated>2023-08-28T14:46:41+00:00</updated>
    <content>How can a candidate be independent if he is dependent on the support of opposition party leaders? Singaporeans are not so easily fooled. There is a real danger that he might be manipulated by political parties serving their own interests if elected. He even suggested that they might be appointed to the Council of Presidential Advisers. This game of backseat politicking dishonours the office of the Presidency. Vote for me 🖐🏼❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272384642949451015" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-28T14:46:41+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272406248706903314</id>
    <title>In general, it is not my preference to campaign reactively and respond to every remark made by the other candidates. I would prefer to win on my own merits, rather than on the demerits of my opponents. But there is a line that must be drawn when it comes </title>
    <updated>2023-08-28T16:10:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>In general, it is not my preference to campaign reactively and respond to every remark made by the other candidates. I would prefer to win on my own merits, rather than on the demerits of my opponents. But there is a line that must be drawn when it comes to those attempting to confuse the electorate. We must be wary of those who make empty promises. This morning at Ayer Rajah Food Centre, I spoke to the media about why certain members of opposition parties coming forward to support Mr Tan Kin Lian does a disservice to Singaporeans and dishonours the office of the President. Private individuals have a right to support whichever candidate they prefer. However, it is plain to see that Mr Tan's supporters are making a coordinated effort to rouse up anti-Government sentiment. Their strategy has been to make populist promises he will not be able to keep. They speak of alleviating bread and butter problems that Singaporeans are facing. It is false to suggest this is something Mr Tan can meaningfully address as President. It is simply not the President's role to address policy matters and he will have no power to do so. It is deceptive and dishonest to pretend otherwise. At lunchtime, I visited Lau Pa Sat and met many young professionals who work in the CBD. I was grateful that my message of non-partisanship resonated so strongly with many of them. In the evening, together with the other candidates, I participated in a forum that was broadcast live on CNA and online. I hope my straightforward answers to the questions will help Singaporeans understand my credentials, intentions and character better so they can make an informed choice at the ballot box. Singaporeans are a savvy lot who are not easily fooled. May the best man win, come Polling Day. 🖐🏼❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272406248706903314" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-28T16:10:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272581769671609607</id>
    <title>All of us have got certain gifts and skills. Good work is the kind of work that brings out the best in you, regardless of your background. I am thankful I did not heed advice to leave the GIC. My job gave me satisfaction because I was able to exploit my t</title>
    <updated>2023-08-29T03:31:39+00:00</updated>
    <content>All of us have got certain gifts and skills. Good work is the kind of work that brings out the best in you, regardless of your background. I am thankful I did not heed advice to leave the GIC. My job gave me satisfaction because I was able to exploit my talent to benefit a greater good — the nation’s financial security. Now, I am ready to use my years of experience to joyfully serve the people of Singapore, as your elected President. I humbly ask for you to give me this chance, as the only non-partisan candidate. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272581769671609607" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-29T03:31:39+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272632514047397127</id>
    <title>Message from Mr Ng Kok Song’s campaign team 🖐🏼❤️</title>
    <updated>2023-08-29T06:48:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>Message from Mr Ng Kok Song’s campaign team 🖐🏼❤️</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272632514047397127" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-29T06:48:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
