<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial</id>
  <title>ngkoksongofficial TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-27T16:15:42+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/ngkoksongofficial.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from ngkoksongofficial</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271607301063200007</id>
    <title>Happy International Dog Day! ❤️ I've actually been saving this very special video with Cotton, and here it is! 🐶👨🏼‍🦳 My family casually filmed this for fun when I made the decision with them that I would want to run for president and serve Singapore! It w</title>
    <updated>2023-08-26T12:30:14+00:00</updated>
    <content>Happy International Dog Day! ❤️ I've actually been saving this very special video with Cotton, and here it is! 🐶👨🏼‍🦳 My family casually filmed this for fun when I made the decision with them that I would want to run for president and serve Singapore! It was a private and personal video. Now looking at this, it makes me so happy that we have actually put my dream into action and that voting day is just next week ! Vote for me! 🖐🏽❤️</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271607301063200007" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-26T12:30:14+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271620272225062152</id>
    <title>I am standing for the presidency as a non-partisan candidate. My whole life, I have worked to be responsible for my family and the people of Singapore.  This year, I stepped up for the presidency because I believe more transparency is needed in the role o</title>
    <updated>2023-08-26T13:20:33+00:00</updated>
    <content>I am standing for the presidency as a non-partisan candidate. My whole life, I have worked to be responsible for my family and the people of Singapore.  This year, I stepped up for the presidency because I believe more transparency is needed in the role of the Presidency. I will ensure our financial, social and administrative treasures are safeguarded without fear or favour.  I will be the president for the people. #unitedforourfuture #ngkoksong2023  🖐🏽❤️ Vote For Me </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271620272225062152" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-26T13:20:33+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271633434794003720</id>
    <title>When it comes to drawing on our reserves, there is a misconception that the smaller the sum, the easier it is for the President to approve it. That may not always be the case. The president has to be competent enough to know what is the situation we’re de</title>
    <updated>2023-08-26T14:11:37+00:00</updated>
    <content>When it comes to drawing on our reserves, there is a misconception that the smaller the sum, the easier it is for the President to approve it. That may not always be the case. The president has to be competent enough to know what is the situation we’re dealing with. In times of crises, a larger than proposed sum may be needed to ensure the survival of Singapore. If we do not act forcefully when needed, we risk losing our jobs and lives. I have enough expertise to make sure the best judgment call is made whenever our reserves are touched. I will make the decision that is best for Singapore. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture 🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271633434794003720" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-26T14:11:37+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271661993252162834</id>
    <title>My first stop for the day was at the vibrant Chong Pang Market, where I was greeted with such enthusiasm by so many Singaporeans who were there for breakfast with their friends, family and pets! A bustling market never fails to energise me in the morning.</title>
    <updated>2023-08-26T16:02:27+00:00</updated>
    <content>My first stop for the day was at the vibrant Chong Pang Market, where I was greeted with such enthusiasm by so many Singaporeans who were there for breakfast with their friends, family and pets! A bustling market never fails to energise me in the morning. In the afternoon, I was back at SPH Media again for another round of interviews, this time with Zaobaosg. The first was a lighthearted couple interview together with Sybil where the producers asked us fun questions and had us write down our answers to see if they would match. Can you guess how many matching answers we got? Check out the full video to find out! Then Sybil and I both took individual interviews with Zaobao reporters, where we took the opportunity to speak in our dialects - me in Teochew and Sybil in Cantonese. I explained how Mandarin was not a compulsory subject in school when I was a boy, so I grew up speaking mainly Teochew and English. I also shared about my childhood friends Dr Lee Boon Yang and Mr Lim Boon Heng - we were all from Hougang villages. We were also Montfort School prefects together, along with my late wife, Pat.  Meanwhile, Sybil shared five items that hold deep meaning for her, including a photograph of her grandfather with world leaders at the 1943 Cairo Conference and a piece of calligraphy she made for our mutual friend Ray Dalio. In the evening, we made a stop at Ang Mo Kio Central Market where I shared with the media why I believe it is time for Singapore to elect a truly non-partisan President who is not beholden to any political party, in keeping with not only the letter of the law but also the spirit of the Constitution. We have matured as a society and as a democracy and we should no longer take it for granted that Presidential candidates must be endorsed by the ruling party to stand a chance. I received several unexpected gifts from the crowd at Ang Mo Kio, including a bouquet of flowers from a precocious little boy and his family as well as a photo book entitled The Red Dot which was produced by father-and-son photography team, Jimmy &amp; Matthew Lam. Every day of this journey has been an adventure. I am so, so grateful for the warm support of everyone who has made time to meet me in person, snap a selfie with me, and ask me questions. Fellow Singaporeans, you are the reason I am standing for President. Thank you all! #unitedforourfuture #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote for Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271661993252162834" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-26T16:02:27+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271881750270233864</id>
    <title>Love is the greatest experience we can have in our lives. One of my fondest memories was the day I fell in love with my wife, Patricia, in school. We went on to share 33 years of love during our marriage. We stood by each other through thick and thin, esp</title>
    <updated>2023-08-27T06:15:15+00:00</updated>
    <content>Love is the greatest experience we can have in our lives. One of my fondest memories was the day I fell in love with my wife, Patricia, in school. We went on to share 33 years of love during our marriage. We stood by each other through thick and thin, especially during the bad times. When she was diagnosed with cancer, I took a year off from work to spend as much time as I could with her. Towards her last few days, she thanked me for loving her because she said it had helped her overcome her fear of death.  I had to take responsibility for her and my kids, as a single dad, after she passed. I had to step up. Now, I want to be responsible for the people of Singapore by standing to be the President. I love my country for all that it has provided me and my family. I want to inspire others to never lose hope too. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote for Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271881750270233864" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-27T06:15:15+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271894098217422088</id>
    <title>As President, I want to bring businesses together to do philanthropy. I want to promote the idea of sharing, not giving. When you are able to give and care, it makes you a kinder person and fills you with joy. You’re benefiting as much as the receiver.  I</title>
    <updated>2023-08-27T07:03:09+00:00</updated>
    <content>As President, I want to bring businesses together to do philanthropy. I want to promote the idea of sharing, not giving. When you are able to give and care, it makes you a kinder person and fills you with joy. You’re benefiting as much as the receiver.  I am determined to foster this culture of giving time and resources to the less fortunate. This might include the migrant workers, the poor and the dying. We should consider structuring volunteerism within companies and organisations. We must remember to be a gracious society ❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote for Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271894098217422088" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-27T07:03:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271915714414447880</id>
    <title>It is critical that we honour the spirit of the Constitution. The President is a unifying figure. He or she should not be beholden to any political parties. I stand as a truly independent candidate with a heart-powered team. I am not backed by any parties</title>
    <updated>2023-08-27T08:27:02+00:00</updated>
    <content>It is critical that we honour the spirit of the Constitution. The President is a unifying figure. He or she should not be beholden to any political parties. I stand as a truly independent candidate with a heart-powered team. I am not backed by any parties, but rather by my record of serving the people of Singapore.  I am driven by love from my family and the people I have met over my life, including the past few weeks. I will safeguard our national treasures based on the best interest of the people. In times of political or other crises, I will make the most objective judgment call. Thank you for standing with me. We stand United for our future. 🖐🏼❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271915714414447880" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-27T08:27:02+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271941267670568200</id>
    <title>We must not allow this Presidential Election to become a proxy fight between the government endorsed candidate and the opposition endorsed candidate. This is dangerous and divisive. Save the party politics for the next General Election and do not let it p</title>
    <updated>2023-08-27T10:06:11+00:00</updated>
    <content>We must not allow this Presidential Election to become a proxy fight between the government endorsed candidate and the opposition endorsed candidate. This is dangerous and divisive. Save the party politics for the next General Election and do not let it pollute the office of the President, which is supposed to be a unifying force. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271941267670568200" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-27T10:06:11+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271983392982453512</id>
    <title>Statement by Salleh Marican on the need for the President to be non-partisan. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture 🖐🏼❤️. </title>
    <updated>2023-08-27T12:49:39+00:00</updated>
    <content>Statement by Salleh Marican on the need for the President to be non-partisan. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture 🖐🏼❤️. </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271983392982453512" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-27T12:49:39+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272036493357534471</id>
    <title>Never a dull day during campaign season! At Tampines Round Market in the morning, I spoke about the importance of ensuring the Elected President is not beholden to any political party. We cannot have a President who may be manipulated to serve the politic</title>
    <updated>2023-08-27T16:15:42+00:00</updated>
    <content>Never a dull day during campaign season! At Tampines Round Market in the morning, I spoke about the importance of ensuring the Elected President is not beholden to any political party. We cannot have a President who may be manipulated to serve the political agenda of any party. By the time I got to Chinatown Complex around lunchtime, news had broken that another opposition party leader had endorsed one of the other candidates. Naturally, the media had many questions for me about this development. I shared my views frankly. Let's not mince words. The move by some members of opposition parties to endorse a certain candidate is dangerous and divisive. Turning the Presidential Election into a proxy for a General Election is a polarising move that aims to force Singaporeans to choose between a government-endorsed candidate and an opposition-endorsed candidate. I am glad that not all opposition parties have decided to do this. Responsible opposition politicians understand the difference between a PE and a GE. They know how important it is to ensure the President remains a unifying force in Singapore and not an office to be used as a backdoor to pressure the Government on policy matters. I was very happy to receive such a warm welcome from Singaporeans at both hawker centres. Many, many people came to say hello, including some who are still too young to vote but have been following the developments closely. Wonderful to see such political awareness among the future electorate. In the evening, I had a more lighthearted session with @Hao on a TikTok livestream where he invited his followers and friends to Ask Me Anything or AMA! We talked about a wide range of topics, including how to deal with personal conflicts, managing one's finances and why the President cannot lower the GST rate. Another AMA video which I had filmed together with Tharman also premiered on Straits Times. We both fielded questions on everything from mental health among youth to how we would celebrate if we won the election. Just a few days left before we go to the polls. I'm going all out to meet as many Singaporeans as I can.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272036493357534471" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-27T16:15:42+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
