<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial</id>
  <title>ngkoksongofficial TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-12-01T05:07:46+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/ngkoksongofficial.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from ngkoksongofficial</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7295252653968264456</id>
    <title>Savouring the lunch Sybil made today for the family. She used lots of hearty ingredients and my heart was definitely full. Even though we’re busy all the time, we make it a point to spend Sundays having a meal together. ❤️ What are you having for lunch to</title>
    <updated>2023-10-29T05:46:14+00:00</updated>
    <content>Savouring the lunch Sybil made today for the family. She used lots of hearty ingredients and my heart was definitely full. Even though we’re busy all the time, we make it a point to spend Sundays having a meal together. ❤️ What are you having for lunch today?</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7295252653968264456" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-29T05:46:14+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7296274576445639954</id>
    <title>I shared my secret to staying healthy at 75, ‘SHIELD’. This acronym was coined by Dr Rudolph Tanzi who specialises in Alzheimer’s and neurology. It is heartening that so many of you guys have picked up on my version of it and helped spread this life-savin</title>
    <updated>2023-10-31T23:51:53+00:00</updated>
    <content>I shared my secret to staying healthy at 75, ‘SHIELD’. This acronym was coined by Dr Rudolph Tanzi who specialises in Alzheimer’s and neurology. It is heartening that so many of you guys have picked up on my version of it and helped spread this life-saving message. When I came to know that Dr. Rudolph Tanzi is on the Scientific Board for Chromadex, it stimulated my interest in his work. He has been a leader in Alzheimer’s research for decades . I started reading up on some of his books , “The Super Brain” and “The Healing Self”, where I came across the wonderful acronym Dr. Tanzi used for healthy lifestyle especially when one is aging - S.H.I.E.L.D. When I had the opportunity to speak with Dr. Tanzi via zoom, I wanted to know how he came up with his acronym. Here is a sneak peek of the conversation. I hope that we continue to spread positive messages like this, so that we can keep the online space a truly beneficial one for all ❤️</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7296274576445639954" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-31T23:51:53+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7297063949218974984</id>
    <title>Max and I would like to wish you a very good morning and a cheerful start to your day! What are your weekend plans? #britishshorthair #mentalhealthmatters #peace #motivation #morningroutine </title>
    <updated>2023-11-03T02:54:59+00:00</updated>
    <content>Max and I would like to wish you a very good morning and a cheerful start to your day! What are your weekend plans? #britishshorthair #mentalhealthmatters #peace #motivation #morningroutine </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7297063949218974984" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-03T02:54:59+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7299309806530088210</id>
    <title>Sybil baked me some oatmeal /flax seed/wheat germ sugar free cookies. They tasted ‘interesting’ but I savoured every bit of it because it was handmade with time and love. ❤️ #healthy #couplegoals #family #breakfast </title>
    <updated>2023-11-09T04:10:04+00:00</updated>
    <content>Sybil baked me some oatmeal /flax seed/wheat germ sugar free cookies. They tasted ‘interesting’ but I savoured every bit of it because it was handmade with time and love. ❤️ #healthy #couplegoals #family #breakfast </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7299309806530088210" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-09T04:10:04+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7299401465947278599</id>
    <title>Very delighted last night that President Tharman and I came together to celebrate the 20th anniversary of Wealth Management Institute which I helped to set up in 2003. </title>
    <updated>2023-11-09T10:05:45+00:00</updated>
    <content>Very delighted last night that President Tharman and I came together to celebrate the 20th anniversary of Wealth Management Institute which I helped to set up in 2003. </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7299401465947278599" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-09T10:05:45+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7300412771571731730</id>
    <title>It takes time to trust someone enough to be comfortable. Papa and I don’t get to spend a lot of time together, but when we do it’s happiness . Happy Deepavali from our family to yours ❤️ — Max #family #deepavali #holidays #britishshorthair #catsoftiktok </title>
    <updated>2023-11-12T03:30:09+00:00</updated>
    <content>It takes time to trust someone enough to be comfortable. Papa and I don’t get to spend a lot of time together, but when we do it’s happiness . Happy Deepavali from our family to yours ❤️ — Max #family #deepavali #holidays #britishshorthair #catsoftiktok </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7300412771571731730" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-12T03:30:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7304971268573383944</id>
    <title>Meditation entered my life at a critical juncture thirty five years ago when I was searching for deeper meaning, purpose and happiness. It took me three years to establish  the daily practice of meditating every morning and evening.  Meditation has transf</title>
    <updated>2023-11-24T10:19:26+00:00</updated>
    <content>Meditation entered my life at a critical juncture thirty five years ago when I was searching for deeper meaning, purpose and happiness. It took me three years to establish  the daily practice of meditating every morning and evening.  Meditation has transformed  my life in my work, relationships and leadership responsibilities by the  cultivation of attention and other- centredness.  From my experience, meditation has been the kindest thing I have done for myself. It is also probably the kindest thing we can do for others because  meditation helps us grow in love, peace and joy. This is why I would like to share with you my practice of meditation so that your life too can be transformed. #meditation #mentalhealth #lifehacks #lifeskills #mentalhealthmatters </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7304971268573383944" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-24T10:19:26+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7306096003776548104</id>
    <title>In this week of ‘Meditation As A Life Skill’ I share the necessary skills you need to begin your meditation journey. Choosing your mantra is important for your practice of Meditation and in fact, your day to day life. Meditation helps us grow in love, pea</title>
    <updated>2023-11-27T11:03:58+00:00</updated>
    <content>In this week of ‘Meditation As A Life Skill’ I share the necessary skills you need to begin your meditation journey. Choosing your mantra is important for your practice of Meditation and in fact, your day to day life. Meditation helps us grow in love, peace and joy.  full video link in bio  #meditation #mentalhealth #mentalhealthawareness #mantra #dailymotivation </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7306096003776548104" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-27T11:03:58+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7306347062562458898</id>
    <title>Started the morning with a game of tennis with my regular buddies! We played a good game and had a hearty chat over roti Prata after (as a reward for keeping fit) 🤣. We talked a little about my new meditation series , the importance of exercise and intera</title>
    <updated>2023-11-28T03:18:17+00:00</updated>
    <content>Started the morning with a game of tennis with my regular buddies! We played a good game and had a hearty chat over roti Prata after (as a reward for keeping fit) 🤣. We talked a little about my new meditation series , the importance of exercise and interacting with people daily for our mental health , financial literacy for all ages and how we can better share our lived experiences. #meditation #tennis #healthylifestyle #lifegoals #lifelessons </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7306347062562458898" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-28T03:18:17+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7307488548993731847</id>
    <title>Meditation helps us tune out distractions by bringing our body and mind to stillness so that we can connect with our spirit. The human body is 3 in 1 — Body, Mind &amp; Spirit. We spend a lot of time developing our minds and bodies but we have neglected nouri</title>
    <updated>2023-12-01T05:07:46+00:00</updated>
    <content>Meditation helps us tune out distractions by bringing our body and mind to stillness so that we can connect with our spirit. The human body is 3 in 1 — Body, Mind &amp; Spirit. We spend a lot of time developing our minds and bodies but we have neglected nourishing our spirit. Here’s some simple steps to help you access your spirit. #meditation #lifegoals #lifehacks #mentalhealth #mentalhealthmatters  full video in bio</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7307488548993731847" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-12-01T05:07:46+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
