<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial</id>
  <title>ngkoksongofficial TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-22T06:54:33+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/ngkoksongofficial.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from ngkoksongofficial</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269561132229152018</id>
    <title>My story is one of hope. I had to give up a scholarship to study overseas, because we were poor and I had to look after my family. My dreams came true when I got myself a bursary. It was my only way out of poverty and I had to work for the government. Tha</title>
    <updated>2023-08-21T00:10:12+00:00</updated>
    <content>My story is one of hope. I had to give up a scholarship to study overseas, because we were poor and I had to look after my family. My dreams came true when I got myself a bursary. It was my only way out of poverty and I had to work for the government. That was how I ended up at MAS and then GIC. I took so much pride in my work because it made me happy. I was able to contribute to growing the reserves for Singapore too. I want to inspire all of you to never give up on your hopes and dreams. I will safeguard your hopes and dreams as your president. Thank you Singapore for everything. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture #family #love #dreamscometrue </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269561132229152018" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-21T00:10:12+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269596362491038994</id>
    <title>The role of the president should evolve with our experience. Our youth are increasingly involved in advocacy and the community. I think the president will be able to unite our country better if he or she evolves to fit the needs of the people too.  I want</title>
    <updated>2023-08-21T02:26:47+00:00</updated>
    <content>The role of the president should evolve with our experience. Our youth are increasingly involved in advocacy and the community. I think the president will be able to unite our country better if he or she evolves to fit the needs of the people too.  I want to teach our youths to be financially literate and help all of us alleviate our stress. Sybil is a huge advocate for the arts and people with special needs. We both will be able to uplift Singaporeans. It will be our honour to be given that chance. #unitedforourfuture #ngkoksong2023</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269596362491038994" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-21T02:26:47+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269670302831955208</id>
    <title>I am so happy to share my list of Proposer, Seconder and Assenters who will be backing my bid to be nominated as a presidential candidate tomorrow. As promised, they are all people of high "heart power" who care deeply about Singapore and Singaporeans. I </title>
    <updated>2023-08-21T07:13:42+00:00</updated>
    <content>I am so happy to share my list of Proposer, Seconder and Assenters who will be backing my bid to be nominated as a presidential candidate tomorrow. As promised, they are all people of high "heart power" who care deeply about Singapore and Singaporeans. I am most grateful for their support. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269670302831955208" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-21T07:13:42+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269705575326371090</id>
    <title>Opened up to Reginald and Dawn from @thefinancialcoconut to share the strategies and risks I took to safeguard Singapore's reserves and what I wish to champion for our nation. Beyond finance, I unveil the impact of my meditation practice on my leadership </title>
    <updated>2023-08-21T09:30:34+00:00</updated>
    <content>Opened up to Reginald and Dawn from @thefinancialcoconut to share the strategies and risks I took to safeguard Singapore's reserves and what I wish to champion for our nation. Beyond finance, I unveil the impact of my meditation practice on my leadership journey. Give it a listen on their platforms! #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269705575326371090" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-21T09:30:34+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269733181136424210</id>
    <title>Love is the greatest gift I have received from life. My mother’s love inspired me to study hard and win a bursary so I would never see her cry again. My late wife Patricia taught me about unconditional love in our 33 years of marriage. When she passed, I </title>
    <updated>2023-08-21T11:17:42+00:00</updated>
    <content>Love is the greatest gift I have received from life. My mother’s love inspired me to study hard and win a bursary so I would never see her cry again. My late wife Patricia taught me about unconditional love in our 33 years of marriage. When she passed, I became a single dad. I learned more about love as I played the roles of mother and father to my youngest daughter. After 14 years of being single, Sybil walked into my life to bless me with newfound love. Thanks to her, I am still learning so much and I am thankful to have her as my equal partner in this journey. I want to give back to Singapore for all the love it has given me. It would be the greatest honour of my life. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture #family #lovewins #nostalgia </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269733181136424210" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-21T11:17:42+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269752509667839239</id>
    <title>As President, I will work with the government for the people. The role of the president is not to make trouble for the government as it will render our nation dysfunctional. We must stay united for our future, while keeping the people at heart. #unitedfor</title>
    <updated>2023-08-21T12:32:43+00:00</updated>
    <content>As President, I will work with the government for the people. The role of the president is not to make trouble for the government as it will render our nation dysfunctional. We must stay united for our future, while keeping the people at heart. #unitedforourfuture #ngkoksong2023 </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269752509667839239" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-21T12:32:43+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269766258608835858</id>
    <title>Singapore is a little red dot. But we are internationally recognised because of our exceptionalism in political and social stability! We cannot take these for granted.  As President, I will use my experience to safeguard this stability. I want to honour o</title>
    <updated>2023-08-21T13:26:01+00:00</updated>
    <content>Singapore is a little red dot. But we are internationally recognised because of our exceptionalism in political and social stability! We cannot take these for granted.  As President, I will use my experience to safeguard this stability. I want to honour our founding fathers and the Merdeka generation — people who have built Singapore for all our future generations. We must not let what we built up be squandered. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture #singapore #singaporetiktok #leekuanyew </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269766258608835858" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-21T13:26:01+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269947787087809799</id>
    <title>Blessed Nomination Day everyone! Sybil usually prepares toast but today is extraordinary - I got a croissant! 🥐 Also, keeping up with my daily discipline of meditation to prepare me for this significant day. Even Max knows it's special! 🐈 #ngkoksong2023 #</title>
    <updated>2023-08-22T01:10:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>Blessed Nomination Day everyone! Sybil usually prepares toast but today is extraordinary - I got a croissant! 🥐 Also, keeping up with my daily discipline of meditation to prepare me for this significant day. Even Max knows it's special! 🐈 #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269947787087809799" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-22T01:10:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270019538987666696</id>
    <title>Last Saturday, I had the opportunity to have a discussion with these change-makers from the creative scene. They are all accomplished in their own fields and shared their thoughts on the future of our arts scene.  I am determined to encourage our youths t</title>
    <updated>2023-08-22T05:48:53+00:00</updated>
    <content>Last Saturday, I had the opportunity to have a discussion with these change-makers from the creative scene. They are all accomplished in their own fields and shared their thoughts on the future of our arts scene.  I am determined to encourage our youths to step into their passions without any fear of security or stability. I was so happy to have had this intimate session with them. I want to do more of these! #unitedforourfuture #ngkoksong2023</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270019538987666696" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-22T05:48:53+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270036458914843912</id>
    <title>I am standing to be your president to protect our three treasures. I will ensure we are united for our future so that Singapore continues to be a beacon of light for the world. We might be of different races — Chinese, Malay, Indian, Eurasian &amp; Others. Bu</title>
    <updated>2023-08-22T06:54:33+00:00</updated>
    <content>I am standing to be your president to protect our three treasures. I will ensure we are united for our future so that Singapore continues to be a beacon of light for the world. We might be of different races — Chinese, Malay, Indian, Eurasian &amp; Others. But we are all Singaporeans. Let us remember our common ground. #unitedforourfuture #ngkoksong2023 </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270036458914843912" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-22T06:54:33+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
