<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial</id>
  <title>ngkoksongofficial TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-24T04:01:29+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/ngkoksongofficial.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from ngkoksongofficial</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270120848890055954</id>
    <title>When I was still in the public service, There was also little risk of a bad government. I was happy in my dream job. Serving the people of Singapore, by growing our reserves strategically was meaningful work. At that stage of my life, that was the best wa</title>
    <updated>2023-08-22T12:22:01+00:00</updated>
    <content>When I was still in the public service, There was also little risk of a bad government. I was happy in my dream job. Serving the people of Singapore, by growing our reserves strategically was meaningful work. At that stage of my life, that was the best way I could contribute to Singapore. Now I want to safeguard the reserves I have helped to grow.  #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270120848890055954" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-22T12:22:01+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270326747562921224</id>
    <title>My fellow Singaporeans,   On National Day, we celebrated the three national treasures that define our country Singapore as exceptional. I am standing for President to protect these three treasures.   The first treasure is our reserves. I can protect the r</title>
    <updated>2023-08-23T01:41:06+00:00</updated>
    <content>My fellow Singaporeans,   On National Day, we celebrated the three national treasures that define our country Singapore as exceptional. I am standing for President to protect these three treasures.   The first treasure is our reserves. I can protect the reserves . I spent my entire career at GIC and MAS helping to build up our reserves.   Our second treasure is good public administration. I have worked in 45 years in public service, I have what it takes to uphold the integrity of [key] public service appointments.   Our third treasure is our social stability, where Singaporeans have lived in peace and harmony, regardless of race, religion or political affiliation. I do not belong to any political party and so I am well placed to unite the people of Singapore to face an uncertain future.   For these three reasons, I humbly ask you, my fellow Singaporeans, to choose me as your President. 我是黄国松，请投我一票 Nama saya Ng Kok Song. Saya berharap anda undilah saya. நான் இங் கொக் சொங். நம்பிக்கையுடன்  எனக்கு வாக்களியுங்கள்!   Thank you. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270326747562921224" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-23T01:41:06+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270367956373196050</id>
    <title>Here’s what mornings look like for me! Toast &amp; kopi while my baby, Max accompanies me. I was sharing with him earlier today that Papa was off to Mediacorp to record a broadcast message. He is very attached 😂❤️! Stay tuned for my message tomorrow when it a</title>
    <updated>2023-08-23T04:20:57+00:00</updated>
    <content>Here’s what mornings look like for me! Toast &amp; kopi while my baby, Max accompanies me. I was sharing with him earlier today that Papa was off to Mediacorp to record a broadcast message. He is very attached 😂❤️! Stay tuned for my message tomorrow when it airs. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture #catsoftiktok #catlovers #cattok </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270367956373196050" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-23T04:20:57+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270431248961654034</id>
    <title>Last Sunday I had the chance to intimately meet with all of these amazing founders and creators! They come from very different and diverse industries. But all of us are Singaporeans, playing a crucial part in the stability of our future. I explained to th</title>
    <updated>2023-08-23T08:26:33+00:00</updated>
    <content>Last Sunday I had the chance to intimately meet with all of these amazing founders and creators! They come from very different and diverse industries. But all of us are Singaporeans, playing a crucial part in the stability of our future. I explained to them the role our reserves play in ensuring sustainable growth for every industry.  I want to help all of us do our part to uplift our nation’s financial literacy. This will ensure a level playing field for our youths and that more people are included in wealth accumulation. As President I am inspired to share my years of knowledge with you. I will also use it to safeguard our reserves with competence and integrity! #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270431248961654034" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-23T08:26:33+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270442035419548935</id>
    <title>This is my official candidate symbol: Five fingers representing Singaporeans of different races and religions, and the heart of the palm representing our common ground. In spite of our differences, we must stand united to face of an uncertain future. I hu</title>
    <updated>2023-08-23T09:08:22+00:00</updated>
    <content>This is my official candidate symbol: Five fingers representing Singaporeans of different races and religions, and the heart of the palm representing our common ground. In spite of our differences, we must stand united to face of an uncertain future. I humbly ask for your vote so I can unite our country as your next President. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270442035419548935" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-23T09:08:22+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270485823378836754</id>
    <title>This is my take on timing the market. I spent 45 years making strategic decisions investing our national reserves. I had to take calculated risks to ensure our nation’s financial wealth accumulated without compromising our stability. I have the necessary </title>
    <updated>2023-08-23T11:58:20+00:00</updated>
    <content>This is my take on timing the market. I spent 45 years making strategic decisions investing our national reserves. I had to take calculated risks to ensure our nation’s financial wealth accumulated without compromising our stability. I have the necessary experience to safeguard our financial defence. I hope to uplift our nation’s financial literacy by sharing more of my knowledge. #unitedforourfuture #ngkoksong2023 #finance #adulting #adultmoney </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270485823378836754" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-23T11:58:20+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270510509659557138</id>
    <title>The best bet I made in the GIC was before the 2008 global financial crisis. I proposed to significantly de-risk the GIC’s portfolio while everyone else was very optimistic about the market. It was tough convincing the board of my contrary recommendation b</title>
    <updated>2023-08-23T13:34:05+00:00</updated>
    <content>The best bet I made in the GIC was before the 2008 global financial crisis. I proposed to significantly de-risk the GIC’s portfolio while everyone else was very optimistic about the market. It was tough convincing the board of my contrary recommendation but I remained firm with the intention to protect our reserves.  I am glad I made the right judgment call and that I had the privilege to work with people who believed in me. As President, I will ensure the best judgment call is made when it comes to safeguarding our reserves. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270510509659557138" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-23T13:34:05+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270543173926014215</id>
    <title>I’m not going to lie, I love playing Mahjong! 😂 Like many of you, I watched my parents play and was intrigued by the strategy it took to master the game. It wasn’t about betting. You have to master memory and observation to strategically plan your move ev</title>
    <updated>2023-08-23T15:40:52+00:00</updated>
    <content>I’m not going to lie, I love playing Mahjong! 😂 Like many of you, I watched my parents play and was intrigued by the strategy it took to master the game. It wasn’t about betting. You have to master memory and observation to strategically plan your move every round. Part of it involves some aspect of risk.  If you’re good at Mahjong, use your interest to develop into life skills! I am sure many of you have what it takes. To bridge the gap in our youth’s financial literacy, we can consider fun ways to educate ourselves! #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270543173926014215" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-23T15:40:52+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270704198767987975</id>
    <title>The first place I went to after my nomination, was Kangkar (Hougang). When my son pointed out the exact spot we used to live in, I was overwhelmed with gratitude and emotions. I had to give up my scholarship to study overseas as my father lost his voice a</title>
    <updated>2023-08-24T02:05:44+00:00</updated>
    <content>The first place I went to after my nomination, was Kangkar (Hougang). When my son pointed out the exact spot we used to live in, I was overwhelmed with gratitude and emotions. I had to give up my scholarship to study overseas as my father lost his voice and could not work. I studied with a local bursary and secured a job in the government to support my family and lift them out of poverty.  I want every Singaporean to know that they can make it in life too. I was just a poor boy from Kangkar. Now, I’m running to be your President. I want to inspire others who don’t have a fair start in life, to never give up on their hopes and dreams. #unitedforourfuture #ngkoksong2023 </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270704198767987975" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-24T02:05:44+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270734025835171090</id>
    <title>After my morning visit to the market today, Max was waiting for me as usual. He is such a good boy and he always gives us his full time and attention. He even understands Teochew! I am always so happy to see him waiting when I open my door! Now, I’m heade</title>
    <updated>2023-08-24T04:01:29+00:00</updated>
    <content>After my morning visit to the market today, Max was waiting for me as usual. He is such a good boy and he always gives us his full time and attention. He even understands Teochew! I am always so happy to see him waiting when I open my door! Now, I’m headed off to meet all of you at these sessions! ❤️ ABC Brickworks Market and Food Centre Time: 12:30pm - 1:30pm Chomp Chomp Food Centre Time: 7:00pm - 8:00pm #unitedforourfuture #ngkoksong2023 #catsoftiktok #catlovers #cats </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270734025835171090" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-24T04:01:29+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
