<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial</id>
  <title>ngkoksongofficial TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-26T16:02:27+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/ngkoksongofficial.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from ngkoksongofficial</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271439134101605650</id>
    <title>Making it a daily ritual to practise my Teochew with Max. Soon he will be my conversation partner for brushing up on my Mandarin too. When I was young, I did not have the opportunity to learn Mandarin as my mother tongue was Teochew and I attended an Engl</title>
    <updated>2023-08-26T01:37:42+00:00</updated>
    <content>Making it a daily ritual to practise my Teochew with Max. Soon he will be my conversation partner for brushing up on my Mandarin too. When I was young, I did not have the opportunity to learn Mandarin as my mother tongue was Teochew and I attended an English school. I regret not picking it up as an adult. But I am a firm believer in lifelong learning, so I will be taking Mandarin lessons after this election - and Max will learn too, since I'll be teaching him as I go! #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271439134101605650" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-26T01:37:42+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271467227444972807</id>
    <title>This week, I visited the Singapore Malay Youth Library Association. Their mission is to ensure vulnerable Malay/Muslim youths are supported and integrated back into society. They employ kindness and attention to rehabilitate them. We must recognise such o</title>
    <updated>2023-08-26T03:26:39+00:00</updated>
    <content>This week, I visited the Singapore Malay Youth Library Association. Their mission is to ensure vulnerable Malay/Muslim youths are supported and integrated back into society. They employ kindness and attention to rehabilitate them. We must recognise such organisations that are doing good work to contribute to our social stability. This is something I want to improve when I am president. We need more interfaith awareness. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏽❤️ Vote For Me </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271467227444972807" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-26T03:26:39+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271490911593417992</id>
    <title>Let's rise above over identifying with just our race or religion! My symbol of the ❤️ in 🖐🏼 means that we may be of different faiths or beliefs, yet when we go deep, we all meet at our common humanity. I have learned so much from different communities. In</title>
    <updated>2023-08-26T04:58:35+00:00</updated>
    <content>Let's rise above over identifying with just our race or religion! My symbol of the ❤️ in 🖐🏼 means that we may be of different faiths or beliefs, yet when we go deep, we all meet at our common humanity. I have learned so much from different communities. Interfaith sharing helps us see our common identity. We are one country, one people. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271490911593417992" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-26T04:58:35+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271539140422798600</id>
    <title>My dear Singaporeans, I have chose to keep my campaign online in order to be sustainable and maximise my reach to our youths. Please share the following message to your family, friends and loved ones so they know me too 🖐🏼❤️ I ask for your vote for three </title>
    <updated>2023-08-26T08:05:43+00:00</updated>
    <content>My dear Singaporeans, I have chose to keep my campaign online in order to be sustainable and maximise my reach to our youths. Please share the following message to your family, friends and loved ones so they know me too 🖐🏼❤️ I ask for your vote for three reasons. First, I am an independent candidate. I do not belong to any political party. I will work with everyone, regardless of political affiliation, to serve the best interests of Singapore. Second, I spent 45 years in public service at MAS and GIC in building our reserves and I will protect it. I will also safeguard the integrity of key appointments in the public service. Third, I have extensive experience working with government leaders and corporate CEOs. I will do Singapore proud on the international stage.  Together, we can build a better and kinder Singapore. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏾❤️ Vote for Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271539140422798600" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-26T08:05:43+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271546915597176082</id>
    <title>When we want to reach out to our youth, we need to be sincere about it. I decided to do my campaign mainly through social media because it was important for me to reach them via the right platform. To know what they’re watching and listening to, allowed m</title>
    <updated>2023-08-26T08:35:55+00:00</updated>
    <content>When we want to reach out to our youth, we need to be sincere about it. I decided to do my campaign mainly through social media because it was important for me to reach them via the right platform. To know what they’re watching and listening to, allowed me to understand firsthand their hopes and fears better. The big thing I learned is how much power technology holds in today’s age. It’s not just about posting selfies. Even the way we take one picture can have so many different meanings. Thank you to all of you for supporting my social media and joining me on my journey. I want to be a President that is sincere in connecting with our future leaders. This is not a charade for me. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐️❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271546915597176082" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-26T08:35:55+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271577041915596039</id>
    <title>I want to make financial literacy accessible to everyone. This will help us uplift our overall wealth without leaving anyone out. When I was young, before I joined the MAS, I knew nothing about bonds or stocks. I was too poor to afford a radio or TV to ke</title>
    <updated>2023-08-26T10:32:49+00:00</updated>
    <content>I want to make financial literacy accessible to everyone. This will help us uplift our overall wealth without leaving anyone out. When I was young, before I joined the MAS, I knew nothing about bonds or stocks. I was too poor to afford a radio or TV to keep up with the news. Today, many disadvantaged youths do not have the access to financial education. It is not something we teach in schools either.  I want to be the president that shares my knowledge and teaches our youths very important life skills. Financial literacy, meditation and public speaking may or may not directly solve their problems. But it will better equip them to face the challenges in life. That is the change I will bring as your president. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture #finance #adulting #lifehacks  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271577041915596039" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-26T10:32:49+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271607301063200007</id>
    <title>Happy International Dog Day! ❤️ I've actually been saving this very special video with Cotton, and here it is! 🐶👨🏼‍🦳 My family casually filmed this for fun when I made the decision with them that I would want to run for president and serve Singapore! It w</title>
    <updated>2023-08-26T12:30:14+00:00</updated>
    <content>Happy International Dog Day! ❤️ I've actually been saving this very special video with Cotton, and here it is! 🐶👨🏼‍🦳 My family casually filmed this for fun when I made the decision with them that I would want to run for president and serve Singapore! It was a private and personal video. Now looking at this, it makes me so happy that we have actually put my dream into action and that voting day is just next week ! Vote for me! 🖐🏽❤️</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271607301063200007" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-26T12:30:14+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271620272225062152</id>
    <title>I am standing for the presidency as a non-partisan candidate. My whole life, I have worked to be responsible for my family and the people of Singapore.  This year, I stepped up for the presidency because I believe more transparency is needed in the role o</title>
    <updated>2023-08-26T13:20:33+00:00</updated>
    <content>I am standing for the presidency as a non-partisan candidate. My whole life, I have worked to be responsible for my family and the people of Singapore.  This year, I stepped up for the presidency because I believe more transparency is needed in the role of the Presidency. I will ensure our financial, social and administrative treasures are safeguarded without fear or favour.  I will be the president for the people. #unitedforourfuture #ngkoksong2023  🖐🏽❤️ Vote For Me </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271620272225062152" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-26T13:20:33+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271633434794003720</id>
    <title>When it comes to drawing on our reserves, there is a misconception that the smaller the sum, the easier it is for the President to approve it. That may not always be the case. The president has to be competent enough to know what is the situation we’re de</title>
    <updated>2023-08-26T14:11:37+00:00</updated>
    <content>When it comes to drawing on our reserves, there is a misconception that the smaller the sum, the easier it is for the President to approve it. That may not always be the case. The president has to be competent enough to know what is the situation we’re dealing with. In times of crises, a larger than proposed sum may be needed to ensure the survival of Singapore. If we do not act forcefully when needed, we risk losing our jobs and lives. I have enough expertise to make sure the best judgment call is made whenever our reserves are touched. I will make the decision that is best for Singapore. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture 🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271633434794003720" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-26T14:11:37+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271661993252162834</id>
    <title>My first stop for the day was at the vibrant Chong Pang Market, where I was greeted with such enthusiasm by so many Singaporeans who were there for breakfast with their friends, family and pets! A bustling market never fails to energise me in the morning.</title>
    <updated>2023-08-26T16:02:27+00:00</updated>
    <content>My first stop for the day was at the vibrant Chong Pang Market, where I was greeted with such enthusiasm by so many Singaporeans who were there for breakfast with their friends, family and pets! A bustling market never fails to energise me in the morning. In the afternoon, I was back at SPH Media again for another round of interviews, this time with Zaobaosg. The first was a lighthearted couple interview together with Sybil where the producers asked us fun questions and had us write down our answers to see if they would match. Can you guess how many matching answers we got? Check out the full video to find out! Then Sybil and I both took individual interviews with Zaobao reporters, where we took the opportunity to speak in our dialects - me in Teochew and Sybil in Cantonese. I explained how Mandarin was not a compulsory subject in school when I was a boy, so I grew up speaking mainly Teochew and English. I also shared about my childhood friends Dr Lee Boon Yang and Mr Lim Boon Heng - we were all from Hougang villages. We were also Montfort School prefects together, along with my late wife, Pat.  Meanwhile, Sybil shared five items that hold deep meaning for her, including a photograph of her grandfather with world leaders at the 1943 Cairo Conference and a piece of calligraphy she made for our mutual friend Ray Dalio. In the evening, we made a stop at Ang Mo Kio Central Market where I shared with the media why I believe it is time for Singapore to elect a truly non-partisan President who is not beholden to any political party, in keeping with not only the letter of the law but also the spirit of the Constitution. We have matured as a society and as a democracy and we should no longer take it for granted that Presidential candidates must be endorsed by the ruling party to stand a chance. I received several unexpected gifts from the crowd at Ang Mo Kio, including a bouquet of flowers from a precocious little boy and his family as well as a photo book entitled The Red Dot which was produced by father-and-son photography team, Jimmy &amp; Matthew Lam. Every day of this journey has been an adventure. I am so, so grateful for the warm support of everyone who has made time to meet me in person, snap a selfie with me, and ask me questions. Fellow Singaporeans, you are the reason I am standing for President. Thank you all! #unitedforourfuture #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote for Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271661993252162834" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-26T16:02:27+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
