<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial</id>
  <title>ngkoksongofficial TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-25T16:03:50+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/ngkoksongofficial.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from ngkoksongofficial</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270842782233808146</id>
    <title>Durian is the secret to happiness 😂! Unfortunately I’ve had to cut down on my durian intake to avoid too much sugar. I know MSW is well-loved but I’m a fan of D24. It is more affordable and it has that hint of bitterness. Just the right mix! Our identity </title>
    <updated>2023-08-24T11:03:30+00:00</updated>
    <content>Durian is the secret to happiness 😂! Unfortunately I’ve had to cut down on my durian intake to avoid too much sugar. I know MSW is well-loved but I’m a fan of D24. It is more affordable and it has that hint of bitterness. Just the right mix! Our identity as the country that loves Durian is just one of many things that keep us United. It makes us smile. This happiness is something I will preserve for our future generations.  #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270842782233808146" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-24T11:03:30+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270858038792293650</id>
    <title>When Pope John Paul II visited Singapore in 1986, the first thing he did after getting off the plane was to kneel down and kiss the tarmac as a sign of respect. I did the same when I visited the site of my childhood home in Kangkar on Tuesday, after being</title>
    <updated>2023-08-24T12:02:41+00:00</updated>
    <content>When Pope John Paul II visited Singapore in 1986, the first thing he did after getting off the plane was to kneel down and kiss the tarmac as a sign of respect. I did the same when I visited the site of my childhood home in Kangkar on Tuesday, after being officially confirmed as a Presidential candidate. It was my way of showing respect to the place I came from and honouring those who came before me, who shaped me into the person I am. I would not be standing as a Presidential candidate today if not for simple love of my parents, who worked hard to support my dreams. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270858038792293650" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-24T12:02:41+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270870200612916498</id>
    <title>Ng Kok Song Presidential Candidate Broadcast speech in English #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</title>
    <updated>2023-08-24T12:49:53+00:00</updated>
    <content>Ng Kok Song Presidential Candidate Broadcast speech in English #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270870200612916498" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-24T12:49:53+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271074452161482002</id>
    <title>Too Kiasi already lah! Singapore is not operating at its full potential yet because we have a culture of being too cautious. I think we can be more creative and adventurous to take some risk. I hold the idea of fun very close to my heart. I want to encour</title>
    <updated>2023-08-25T02:02:30+00:00</updated>
    <content>Too Kiasi already lah! Singapore is not operating at its full potential yet because we have a culture of being too cautious. I think we can be more creative and adventurous to take some risk. I hold the idea of fun very close to my heart. I want to encourage fun ways for our youths to educate themselves! This will ultimately help us be more competitive and prosperous.#ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271074452161482002" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-25T02:02:30+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271123441485450514</id>
    <title>am standing as a true non-partisan Presidential candidate and I have never had any affiliation with political parties. I will be able to discharge my duties without fear or favour. I will be able to serve all Singaporeans in their best interests while wor</title>
    <updated>2023-08-25T05:12:36+00:00</updated>
    <content>am standing as a true non-partisan Presidential candidate and I have never had any affiliation with political parties. I will be able to discharge my duties without fear or favour. I will be able to serve all Singaporeans in their best interests while working with the government. The people of Singapore needs someone who is familiar with the machinery of the government yet is non-partisan. I am that person. #unitedforourfuture #ngkoksong2023  🖐🏽❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271123441485450514" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-25T05:12:36+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271151362652523783</id>
    <title>I was given the opportunity to share with the leaders of Taman Bacaan my gratitude to the Malay and Muslim communities for the backing of Salleh, Ameer, Hamid as my assenters. Taman Bacaan and I had also talked about the idea of building more interracial </title>
    <updated>2023-08-25T07:00:56+00:00</updated>
    <content>I was given the opportunity to share with the leaders of Taman Bacaan my gratitude to the Malay and Muslim communities for the backing of Salleh, Ameer, Hamid as my assenters. Taman Bacaan and I had also talked about the idea of building more interracial help so that we can all be more invested in each other's communities and that is crucial for our long-term stability. They also talked about the deep kindness they want to see in Singapore. I felt the force of it. Thank you, Taman Bacaan! #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏽❤️ Vote for Me </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271151362652523783" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-25T07:00:56+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271184150768438536</id>
    <title>After an exciting interview today, I came back to rest before bringing Max for his daily walk. He looks forward to these walks and it is our special family time together. I’ll be headed out again soon to Kent Ridge Guild House for ‘Meet The Presidential C</title>
    <updated>2023-08-25T09:08:10+00:00</updated>
    <content>After an exciting interview today, I came back to rest before bringing Max for his daily walk. He looks forward to these walks and it is our special family time together. I’ll be headed out again soon to Kent Ridge Guild House for ‘Meet The Presidential Candidate Series’ hosted by Prof Walid! Many of you have asked me if this will be live-streamed. It won’t be but I will be sharing some of the insights on social media this week. I am excited to meet more amazing Singaporeans soon! #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture #catsoftiktok #cats #britishshorthaircat  🖐🏽❤️ Vote for Me </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271184150768438536" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-25T09:08:10+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271263141714021640</id>
    <title>I know Sybil to be a successful, accomplished and mature woman. She has seen life and has been through enough experiences to develop her own values. She adds so much more dimension and perspective into how I view things. I was single for 14 years after my</title>
    <updated>2023-08-25T14:14:41+00:00</updated>
    <content>I know Sybil to be a successful, accomplished and mature woman. She has seen life and has been through enough experiences to develop her own values. She adds so much more dimension and perspective into how I view things. I was single for 14 years after my wife Patricia passed of cancer. When I met Sybil, I was amazed by her beauty, brains and character. She celebrates strong women in all that she does, and I could not be prouder to call her my partner. ❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271263141714021640" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-25T14:14:41+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271276394787654920</id>
    <title>I am focusing my campaign efforts on social media because I believe it is the most effective way to reach all of you. I find it important to make sure my messaging is aligned with our youths and current society. Through this process I’ve also picked up so</title>
    <updated>2023-08-25T15:06:07+00:00</updated>
    <content>I am focusing my campaign efforts on social media because I believe it is the most effective way to reach all of you. I find it important to make sure my messaging is aligned with our youths and current society. Through this process I’ve also picked up some TikTok tricks from my young social media team 😂. I hear some concerns of missing out on reaching the older audience.  Fret not, I am doing as much walkabouts as I can, to meet them face to face. It is important to be sustainable. I want to be a President that is able to connect to the future of our country — our youths. I believe my strategy has allowed me to hear their fears, hopes and dreams the best way possible. And I am thankful. ❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271276394787654920" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-25T15:06:07+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271291268209200392</id>
    <title>No walkabouts today but I was certainly kept busy. Visited SPH Media this morning for a filming session at The Straits Times newsroom with fellow candidate Tharman, but I won't spoil what it was about. Keep a lookout for the video soon!  I also invited Je</title>
    <updated>2023-08-25T16:03:50+00:00</updated>
    <content>No walkabouts today but I was certainly kept busy. Visited SPH Media this morning for a filming session at The Straits Times newsroom with fellow candidate Tharman, but I won't spoil what it was about. Keep a lookout for the video soon!  I also invited Jean from ST into my car for a quick interview on the way to the next campaign stop. We had a nice chat about how I'm keeping my energy levels up during this very busy season and how my loved ones are supporting me both on the ground and behind the scenes. In the afternoon, I took my cat Max for a short walk around the block before meeting reporters from Mothership for another interview. We took a look back at key moments in my campaign so far and I reflected on the highs and lows. Always good to take stock at halftime and strategise for the endgame. In the evening, I reunited with Prof Walid, this time in person, for a dialogue at the NUSS Kent Ridge Guild House with NUSS members. Let me tell you, the audience did not pull their punches! My social media team livestreamed part of the Q&amp;A session on Instagram and will upload a video of the full session as well as some clips soon. I shared with the audience why I felt compelled to run for the presidency, and what I plan to do with my salary if I am elected as President. Finally, I made a quick stop at Newton Food Centre for some fried Hokkien mee for supper. Some young Singaporeans who also were also feeling peckish recognised me from my social media videos and we took some selfies together. I will resume my public walkabouts tomorrow with visits to Chong Pang, Gardens by the Bay and Ang Mo Kio. Hope to catch some of you in person! #unitedforourfuture #ngkoksong2023  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271291268209200392" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-25T16:03:50+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
