<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial</id>
  <title>ngkoksongofficial TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-21T00:10:12+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/ngkoksongofficial.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from ngkoksongofficial</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269006468064595208</id>
    <title>The elected president needs to have the right experience and knowledge of how our economy is related to the global economy. This will ensure the president knows how to make a judgment call when it comes to safeguarding the reserves. #ngkoksong2023 #united</title>
    <updated>2023-08-19T12:17:40+00:00</updated>
    <content>The elected president needs to have the right experience and knowledge of how our economy is related to the global economy. This will ensure the president knows how to make a judgment call when it comes to safeguarding the reserves. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269006468064595208" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-19T12:17:40+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269035265530858759</id>
    <title>True happiness comes from caring for others. When I was at GIC, I derived happiness from contributing to the welfare of Singaporeans. So whatever you do, consider asking yourself ‘how can I contribute to the happiness and welfare of another person?’  Acts</title>
    <updated>2023-08-19T14:09:25+00:00</updated>
    <content>True happiness comes from caring for others. When I was at GIC, I derived happiness from contributing to the welfare of Singaporeans. So whatever you do, consider asking yourself ‘how can I contribute to the happiness and welfare of another person?’  Acts of kindness and generosity expand your being. But when you are self centred, you contract into your ego. You have to understand this through your experiences in life ❤️  #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture #lifehacks #adulting #happiness </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269035265530858759" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-19T14:09:25+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269201802032205063</id>
    <title>Philanthropy is not just the giving of money. Companies in Singapore could do more to promote this idea of structured volunteerism. It means establishing a way for employees to contribute to community work.  Encourage staff to go down to the ground and do</title>
    <updated>2023-08-20T00:55:48+00:00</updated>
    <content>Philanthropy is not just the giving of money. Companies in Singapore could do more to promote this idea of structured volunteerism. It means establishing a way for employees to contribute to community work.  Encourage staff to go down to the ground and do simple things such as distributing food to the poor. It doesn’t cost a lot of money but it costs time. So the leadership of these organisations must set an example. 🙌 #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture #adulting #happiness #love </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269201802032205063" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-20T00:55:48+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269217997858901266</id>
    <title>Testimonial for Ng Kok Song By Tjio Kay Loen Former Assistant General Manager, OCBC  #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </title>
    <updated>2023-08-20T01:58:33+00:00</updated>
    <content>Testimonial for Ng Kok Song By Tjio Kay Loen Former Assistant General Manager, OCBC  #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269217997858901266" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-20T01:58:33+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269249056851987719</id>
    <title>Stepping into the markets after receiving my Certificate of Eligibility felt like a dream. When I was a kid, I spent most of time helping my dad at the fish market. Now I’m running to be your elected President. My dream has always been to be able to serve</title>
    <updated>2023-08-20T03:59:03+00:00</updated>
    <content>Stepping into the markets after receiving my Certificate of Eligibility felt like a dream. When I was a kid, I spent most of time helping my dad at the fish market. Now I’m running to be your elected President. My dream has always been to be able to serve others. After working in the GIC for 45 years, serving the welfare of Singaporeans, I am honoured to be able to serve again. I will honour the hopes and dreams of our past, present and future generations. Thank you Singapore! #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture #dreamscometrue #lifegoals #goals </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269249056851987719" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-20T03:59:03+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269299213513559314</id>
    <title>I loved at my job at the GIC too much because it was a job that brought out the best in me. I found meaning in it because I was not working for the shareholders of Goldman Sachs. I was working to build up the reserves for the people of Singapore. Now I wa</title>
    <updated>2023-08-20T07:13:41+00:00</updated>
    <content>I loved at my job at the GIC too much because it was a job that brought out the best in me. I found meaning in it because I was not working for the shareholders of Goldman Sachs. I was working to build up the reserves for the people of Singapore. Now I want to help safeguard these reserves as President.  When you have a job that brings out the best in you and benefits others, that is good work. Consider asking yourself, what is it that brings out the best in you?  #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269299213513559314" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-20T07:13:41+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269313776560655634</id>
    <title>Some friends heard about the two bookends of my career which I shared at a @Mothership interview, and asked to read them. The first was a testimonial from my school teacher when I graduated from Montfort School. The second was a letter from PM Lee Hsien L</title>
    <updated>2023-08-20T08:10:11+00:00</updated>
    <content>Some friends heard about the two bookends of my career which I shared at a @Mothership interview, and asked to read them. The first was a testimonial from my school teacher when I graduated from Montfort School. The second was a letter from PM Lee Hsien Loong when I retired from GIC. These two documents are the bookends of my career. #unitedforourfuture #ngkoksong2023 </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269313776560655634" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-20T08:10:11+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269348759472049415</id>
    <title>I got the chance to share about my long commitment to our financial defence with @l@ZYRUP Media. I talked about the strategies I proposed and executed in GIC. It was my dream job because I found happiness in contributing to the welfare of Singaporeans. It</title>
    <updated>2023-08-20T10:25:57+00:00</updated>
    <content>I got the chance to share about my long commitment to our financial defence with @l@ZYRUP Media. I talked about the strategies I proposed and executed in GIC. It was my dream job because I found happiness in contributing to the welfare of Singaporeans. It is great to see you guys invested in politics too. Also, congrats on the success of your podcast. Stay tuned for this episode tomorrow 👏 #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269348759472049415" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-20T10:25:57+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269371512803626248</id>
    <title>Sybil spoke to @Mothership to share her personal stories. Sybil is a rather private person but she hopes for more people to understand her better. She talks about our relationship, her mum, and her philanthropy! Can’t give too much away as this is her sto</title>
    <updated>2023-08-20T11:54:11+00:00</updated>
    <content>Sybil spoke to @Mothership to share her personal stories. Sybil is a rather private person but she hopes for more people to understand her better. She talks about our relationship, her mum, and her philanthropy! Can’t give too much away as this is her story to tell. Stay tuned for the interview out soon! Thank you for being by my side through this journey. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture #womenoftiktok #womenempowerment #womenpower </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269371512803626248" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-20T11:54:11+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269561132229152018</id>
    <title>My story is one of hope. I had to give up a scholarship to study overseas, because we were poor and I had to look after my family. My dreams came true when I got myself a bursary. It was my only way out of poverty and I had to work for the government. Tha</title>
    <updated>2023-08-21T00:10:12+00:00</updated>
    <content>My story is one of hope. I had to give up a scholarship to study overseas, because we were poor and I had to look after my family. My dreams came true when I got myself a bursary. It was my only way out of poverty and I had to work for the government. That was how I ended up at MAS and then GIC. I took so much pride in my work because it made me happy. I was able to contribute to growing the reserves for Singapore too. I want to inspire all of you to never give up on your hopes and dreams. I will safeguard your hopes and dreams as your president. Thank you Singapore for everything. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture #family #love #dreamscometrue </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7269561132229152018" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-21T00:10:12+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
