<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial</id>
  <title>ngkoksongofficial TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-18T12:50:37+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/ngkoksongofficial.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from ngkoksongofficial</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7267766636462034194</id>
    <title>I was in public service for 45 years. I know how important it is to uphold the integrity of our key appointment holders. It is not just about conforming to the letter of the law. It is also about honouring the spirit of the law! #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforo</title>
    <updated>2023-08-16T04:06:42+00:00</updated>
    <content>I was in public service for 45 years. I know how important it is to uphold the integrity of our key appointment holders. It is not just about conforming to the letter of the law. It is also about honouring the spirit of the law! #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7267766636462034194" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-16T04:06:42+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7267798096174746887</id>
    <title>The elected president has the role of safeguarding our 3 treasures. These treasures make Singapore an exceptional country. So it is imperative that the president has the right experience to protect these treasures. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </title>
    <updated>2023-08-16T06:08:45+00:00</updated>
    <content>The elected president has the role of safeguarding our 3 treasures. These treasures make Singapore an exceptional country. So it is imperative that the president has the right experience to protect these treasures. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7267798096174746887" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-16T06:08:45+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7267859979309239559</id>
    <title>If there's something I can't do so well... that would be cooking! 🤣 I hand made some pizza the other night which I think was absolutely delicious! Sybil said it was burnt and she was not impressed, but she ate it anyway and even took many photos. I was so</title>
    <updated>2023-08-16T10:08:43+00:00</updated>
    <content>If there's something I can't do so well... that would be cooking! 🤣 I hand made some pizza the other night which I think was absolutely delicious! Sybil said it was burnt and she was not impressed, but she ate it anyway and even took many photos. I was so happy 😊 #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture #pizza #dinner #datenight </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7267859979309239559" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-16T10:08:43+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7268101230025575688</id>
    <title>Testimonial for Ng Kok Song By Dawa Tarchin Phillips Global Transformational Leader CEO of Empowerment Holdings Consultancy for Business Leaders #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </title>
    <updated>2023-08-17T01:44:56+00:00</updated>
    <content>Testimonial for Ng Kok Song By Dawa Tarchin Phillips Global Transformational Leader CEO of Empowerment Holdings Consultancy for Business Leaders #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7268101230025575688" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-17T01:44:56+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7268135866743229704</id>
    <title>In all my professional career, I have never courted limelight. I was focused on generating returns for Singapore. For this Presidential Election, I have been working hard to tell my stories to Singaporeans. I want you guys to know me for who I am and I ho</title>
    <updated>2023-08-17T03:59:17+00:00</updated>
    <content>In all my professional career, I have never courted limelight. I was focused on generating returns for Singapore. For this Presidential Election, I have been working hard to tell my stories to Singaporeans. I want you guys to know me for who I am and I hope to have your support. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7268135866743229704" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-17T03:59:17+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7268258699553131784</id>
    <title>Our food centres are precious communal grounds, for everyone to sit together and enjoy the wonderful diverse cuisines. I hope we can keep the tradition for many more generations to come. We must help our hawkers in whatever ways we can to ensure their sus</title>
    <updated>2023-08-17T11:55:57+00:00</updated>
    <content>Our food centres are precious communal grounds, for everyone to sit together and enjoy the wonderful diverse cuisines. I hope we can keep the tradition for many more generations to come. We must help our hawkers in whatever ways we can to ensure their sustainability. What is your favourite local dish? Mine is meepok! #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7268258699553131784" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-17T11:55:57+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7268471929856740616</id>
    <title>Testimonial for Ng Kok Song By Eric Ching Former Treasury Manager, Citibank Former Treasury Manager, OCBC #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </title>
    <updated>2023-08-18T01:43:33+00:00</updated>
    <content>Testimonial for Ng Kok Song By Eric Ching Former Treasury Manager, Citibank Former Treasury Manager, OCBC #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7268471929856740616" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-18T01:43:33+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7268513233420569864</id>
    <title>I'm glad that our hawker centres are easily accessible to enjoy local favourites, allowing us to bond and connect over makan.  To the many hawkers and members of public whom I have met - thank you for all the warmth and support! As an independent candidat</title>
    <updated>2023-08-18T04:23:47+00:00</updated>
    <content>I'm glad that our hawker centres are easily accessible to enjoy local favourites, allowing us to bond and connect over makan.  To the many hawkers and members of public whom I have met - thank you for all the warmth and support! As an independent candidate, I appreciate all of you ❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture #foodtiktok #hawker #vibes </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7268513233420569864" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-18T04:23:47+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7268526479217151239</id>
    <title>10.26am, 18 August 2023, marks the start of my official journey as a Presidential Candidate to continue to serve all Singaporeans. The Presidential Elections Committee has issued me the Certificate of Eligibility. As I reflect, I would like to honour the </title>
    <updated>2023-08-18T05:15:09+00:00</updated>
    <content>10.26am, 18 August 2023, marks the start of my official journey as a Presidential Candidate to continue to serve all Singaporeans. The Presidential Elections Committee has issued me the Certificate of Eligibility. As I reflect, I would like to honour the generations before me who built the strong foundation of Singapore. For all of us, here and now, let's do our best for the current and future generations to realise our hopes and ensure that Singapore continues to thrive. I will give my very best to this Presidential bid, as I seek the privilege to be of service and build a united Singapore for the future. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7268526479217151239" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-18T05:15:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7268643880243858695</id>
    <title>Spent time with @Hao and dad on their new podcast! It's been such a joy learning from our youths! Social media has been a level playing field for an independent candidate like  myself. To all my online friends supporting my efforts in this presidential el</title>
    <updated>2023-08-18T12:50:37+00:00</updated>
    <content>Spent time with @Hao and dad on their new podcast! It's been such a joy learning from our youths! Social media has been a level playing field for an independent candidate like  myself. To all my online friends supporting my efforts in this presidential election, thank you. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7268643880243858695" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-18T12:50:37+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
