<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial</id>
  <title>ngkoksongofficial TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-29T08:57:59+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/ngkoksongofficial.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from ngkoksongofficial</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272328184421567752</id>
    <title>Dear Singaporeans, we must not get confused between the Presidential Election and the General Election. Members of some opposition parties have banded together to show their support for one of the other candidates. Another candidate is endorsed by the gov</title>
    <updated>2023-08-28T11:07:35+00:00</updated>
    <content>Dear Singaporeans, we must not get confused between the Presidential Election and the General Election. Members of some opposition parties have banded together to show their support for one of the other candidates. Another candidate is endorsed by the governing party. We must not let them turn this into a proxy fight between the Government and the opposition. This election is not about that. It is about all the people of Singapore, regardless of political affiliations.  The President must be a unifying force, not another source of division and discord. Those who wish to fight it out in the political arena should wait for the next GE. Stand united with me in solidarity to uphold the integrity and honour of the President’s office. 🖐🏼❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272328184421567752" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-28T11:07:35+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272346659336555794</id>
    <title>I will not stand for politicians making a mockery out of our Presidency. Since independence, Singapore has been recognised internationally for its exceptional political and social stability. Our founding leaders and our past generations have worked hard i</title>
    <updated>2023-08-28T12:19:17+00:00</updated>
    <content>I will not stand for politicians making a mockery out of our Presidency. Since independence, Singapore has been recognised internationally for its exceptional political and social stability. Our founding leaders and our past generations have worked hard in unity to lift us out of poverty into a first-world country. It is critical now, more than ever, that our head of state is able to navigate Singapore through crises. The office must be respected and honoured. I stand as a non partisan candidate, not beholden to anyone. I will not be pressured by partisan interests. I want to serve the people of Singapore honourably. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272346659336555794" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-28T12:19:17+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272372802202766599</id>
    <title>Diversity is our strength. Don't let our differences divide us. Staying united is how we stay strong in the face of an uncertain future, and protecting that unity is a key role of the President. I want to be a President for all, a President who is not beh</title>
    <updated>2023-08-28T14:00:43+00:00</updated>
    <content>Diversity is our strength. Don't let our differences divide us. Staying united is how we stay strong in the face of an uncertain future, and protecting that unity is a key role of the President. I want to be a President for all, a President who is not beholden to any political agenda, to rally our people around our common goals and shared dreams. Please, don't let partisanship pollute the Presidency. Help me safeguard our social fabric. Vote for me 🖐🏼❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272372802202766599" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-28T14:00:43+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272384642949451015</id>
    <title>How can a candidate be independent if he is dependent on the support of opposition party leaders? Singaporeans are not so easily fooled. There is a real danger that he might be manipulated by political parties serving their own interests if elected. He ev</title>
    <updated>2023-08-28T14:46:41+00:00</updated>
    <content>How can a candidate be independent if he is dependent on the support of opposition party leaders? Singaporeans are not so easily fooled. There is a real danger that he might be manipulated by political parties serving their own interests if elected. He even suggested that they might be appointed to the Council of Presidential Advisers. This game of backseat politicking dishonours the office of the Presidency. Vote for me 🖐🏼❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272384642949451015" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-28T14:46:41+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272406248706903314</id>
    <title>In general, it is not my preference to campaign reactively and respond to every remark made by the other candidates. I would prefer to win on my own merits, rather than on the demerits of my opponents. But there is a line that must be drawn when it comes </title>
    <updated>2023-08-28T16:10:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>In general, it is not my preference to campaign reactively and respond to every remark made by the other candidates. I would prefer to win on my own merits, rather than on the demerits of my opponents. But there is a line that must be drawn when it comes to those attempting to confuse the electorate. We must be wary of those who make empty promises. This morning at Ayer Rajah Food Centre, I spoke to the media about why certain members of opposition parties coming forward to support Mr Tan Kin Lian does a disservice to Singaporeans and dishonours the office of the President. Private individuals have a right to support whichever candidate they prefer. However, it is plain to see that Mr Tan's supporters are making a coordinated effort to rouse up anti-Government sentiment. Their strategy has been to make populist promises he will not be able to keep. They speak of alleviating bread and butter problems that Singaporeans are facing. It is false to suggest this is something Mr Tan can meaningfully address as President. It is simply not the President's role to address policy matters and he will have no power to do so. It is deceptive and dishonest to pretend otherwise. At lunchtime, I visited Lau Pa Sat and met many young professionals who work in the CBD. I was grateful that my message of non-partisanship resonated so strongly with many of them. In the evening, together with the other candidates, I participated in a forum that was broadcast live on CNA and online. I hope my straightforward answers to the questions will help Singaporeans understand my credentials, intentions and character better so they can make an informed choice at the ballot box. Singaporeans are a savvy lot who are not easily fooled. May the best man win, come Polling Day. 🖐🏼❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272406248706903314" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-28T16:10:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272581769671609607</id>
    <title>All of us have got certain gifts and skills. Good work is the kind of work that brings out the best in you, regardless of your background. I am thankful I did not heed advice to leave the GIC. My job gave me satisfaction because I was able to exploit my t</title>
    <updated>2023-08-29T03:31:39+00:00</updated>
    <content>All of us have got certain gifts and skills. Good work is the kind of work that brings out the best in you, regardless of your background. I am thankful I did not heed advice to leave the GIC. My job gave me satisfaction because I was able to exploit my talent to benefit a greater good — the nation’s financial security. Now, I am ready to use my years of experience to joyfully serve the people of Singapore, as your elected President. I humbly ask for you to give me this chance, as the only non-partisan candidate. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272581769671609607" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-29T03:31:39+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272632514047397127</id>
    <title>Message from Mr Ng Kok Song’s campaign team 🖐🏼❤️</title>
    <updated>2023-08-29T06:48:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>Message from Mr Ng Kok Song’s campaign team 🖐🏼❤️</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272632514047397127" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-29T06:48:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272641399898639623</id>
    <title>Leonard Cohen’s Anthem is one of my favourite songs. It reminds us that it is perfectly okay to be imperfect.  We must keep doing things that matter to us and trying our best. With experience and reflection, we improve. This is a very powerful life lesson</title>
    <updated>2023-08-29T07:23:02+00:00</updated>
    <content>Leonard Cohen’s Anthem is one of my favourite songs. It reminds us that it is perfectly okay to be imperfect.  We must keep doing things that matter to us and trying our best. With experience and reflection, we improve. This is a very powerful life lesson I hope to encourage everyone to hold on to. Through this campaign, I am learning so much from our youths and the power of social media. I am made aware of our diverse hopes, dreams and causes we all champion. I will continue to deepen my understanding so we develop a Singapore for all. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  Vote For Me  🖐🏼❤️</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272641399898639623" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-29T07:23:02+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272651714140900626</id>
    <title>Here’s a very personal interview I did a while back with @Mothership . I shared with them the 3 most important things in my life. I am thankful for my experiences in life. I took responsibility to lift my family out of poverty by winning myself a bursary.</title>
    <updated>2023-08-29T08:03:03+00:00</updated>
    <content>Here’s a very personal interview I did a while back with @Mothership . I shared with them the 3 most important things in my life. I am thankful for my experiences in life. I took responsibility to lift my family out of poverty by winning myself a bursary. When I was the GIC, I took responsibility for growing our reserves and navigating financial crises. When my wife was dying of cancer, I took responsibility to spend every day with her to make sure she knew she was loved. Now, I am ready to be responsible for the people of Singapore as your President. I want us to be United for our future. 🖐🏼❤️#ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272651714140900626" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-29T08:03:03+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272665870663535890</id>
    <title>The value of our reserves is strategically important and must be kept a secret. It is dangerous to suggest that the Government should reveal this information publicly, which would only benefit our enemies. This goes against our national interest and leave</title>
    <updated>2023-08-29T08:57:59+00:00</updated>
    <content>The value of our reserves is strategically important and must be kept a secret. It is dangerous to suggest that the Government should reveal this information publicly, which would only benefit our enemies. This goes against our national interest and leave the Singapore Dollar vulnerable to attack or manipulation.  If elected President, I will want to know how much we have in the reserves, what proportion is set aside for future generations and how much is to be used to benefit the current generation. But I will keep our secrets safe. With my years of experience in the GIC building up our reserves, I will ask the right questions and work with the Government to ensure they are used prudently. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  Vote For Me  🖐🏼❤️</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272665870663535890" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-29T08:57:59+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
