<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial</id>
  <title>ngkoksongofficial TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-25T09:08:10+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/ngkoksongofficial.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from ngkoksongofficial</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270820201988427026</id>
    <title>I love reaching out face to face at markets! I appreciate all of you coming up to connect with me in real life. Thank you for showing me your support and do bring your friends and family along. See you at Chomp Chomp at 7! If you’re nearby, do catch me. O</title>
    <updated>2023-08-24T09:35:51+00:00</updated>
    <content>I love reaching out face to face at markets! I appreciate all of you coming up to connect with me in real life. Thank you for showing me your support and do bring your friends and family along. See you at Chomp Chomp at 7! If you’re nearby, do catch me. Otherwise stay tuned for my broadcast that airs at the following timings! 7pm: CNA for television; CNA938, Money FM 89.3, One FM 91.3, Kiss92 FM &amp; Power 98 for radio 9.30pm: Channel 5 for television; Class 95 &amp; Gold 905 for radio 🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270820201988427026" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-24T09:35:51+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270828048335916295</id>
    <title>We should be extremely proud of the culture of respect Singaporeans have for everyone — regardless of race, language or religion. It is one of our national treasures. With the increase of divisive forces, it is even more important that we safeguard this t</title>
    <updated>2023-08-24T10:06:18+00:00</updated>
    <content>We should be extremely proud of the culture of respect Singaporeans have for everyone — regardless of race, language or religion. It is one of our national treasures. With the increase of divisive forces, it is even more important that we safeguard this treasure. My role of president would be ensuring that we remain United even in the future. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270828048335916295" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-24T10:06:18+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270842782233808146</id>
    <title>Durian is the secret to happiness 😂! Unfortunately I’ve had to cut down on my durian intake to avoid too much sugar. I know MSW is well-loved but I’m a fan of D24. It is more affordable and it has that hint of bitterness. Just the right mix! Our identity </title>
    <updated>2023-08-24T11:03:30+00:00</updated>
    <content>Durian is the secret to happiness 😂! Unfortunately I’ve had to cut down on my durian intake to avoid too much sugar. I know MSW is well-loved but I’m a fan of D24. It is more affordable and it has that hint of bitterness. Just the right mix! Our identity as the country that loves Durian is just one of many things that keep us United. It makes us smile. This happiness is something I will preserve for our future generations.  #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270842782233808146" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-24T11:03:30+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270858038792293650</id>
    <title>When Pope John Paul II visited Singapore in 1986, the first thing he did after getting off the plane was to kneel down and kiss the tarmac as a sign of respect. I did the same when I visited the site of my childhood home in Kangkar on Tuesday, after being</title>
    <updated>2023-08-24T12:02:41+00:00</updated>
    <content>When Pope John Paul II visited Singapore in 1986, the first thing he did after getting off the plane was to kneel down and kiss the tarmac as a sign of respect. I did the same when I visited the site of my childhood home in Kangkar on Tuesday, after being officially confirmed as a Presidential candidate. It was my way of showing respect to the place I came from and honouring those who came before me, who shaped me into the person I am. I would not be standing as a Presidential candidate today if not for simple love of my parents, who worked hard to support my dreams. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270858038792293650" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-24T12:02:41+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270870200612916498</id>
    <title>Ng Kok Song Presidential Candidate Broadcast speech in English #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</title>
    <updated>2023-08-24T12:49:53+00:00</updated>
    <content>Ng Kok Song Presidential Candidate Broadcast speech in English #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270870200612916498" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-24T12:49:53+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270912926221962504</id>
    <title>I had a hectic but rewarding day full of meaningful interactions today. Started bright and early for a visit to Ghim Moh Market, where I explained that I am funding my campaign from my own savings and not accepting any political donations because I do not</title>
    <updated>2023-08-24T15:35:42+00:00</updated>
    <content>I had a hectic but rewarding day full of meaningful interactions today. Started bright and early for a visit to Ghim Moh Market, where I explained that I am funding my campaign from my own savings and not accepting any political donations because I do not want to be beholden to anyone in my bid for the presidency. I also shared my views on why the President may have difficulty acting in a truly objective manner if he or she has too close a relationship with the Prime Minister of the day. I also met many residents and market visitors, including some old colleagues from GIC! After a quick stop at home to freshen up and have a chat with Max (in Teochew!), I was off to the iconic ABC Brickworks Market to meet more Singaporeans. One of them invited me to join him in a rousing rendition of The Moon Represents My Heart (Yue Liang Dai Biao Wo De Xin) and I gladly obliged!  In the late afternoon, Sybil and I had a deeply meaningful time visiting Kwong Wai Shiu Hospital where we learned more about the important work they do to ease the suffering of the less fortunate and the elderly. This time, I was not there as the main guest but as Sybil's companion! The hospital had invited her to visit after learning of her philanthropy work, especially in the fields of healthcare and elder care. My Presidential Candidate Broadcast also aired on TV today, in which I shared with Singaporeans why it is high time we had a President who is truly non-partisan for a change — that is, one with no ties to any political party. Finally, we rounded off the day with a delicious plate of satay bee hoon and more warm conversations with fellow Singaporeans and food lovers at Chomp Chomp Food Centre. I was very touched to see one resident brandishing a styrofoam sign that said Vote NKS! There's just one week left for campaigning. I'm ready to give it my all. See you on the ground! #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7270912926221962504" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-24T15:35:42+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271074452161482002</id>
    <title>Too Kiasi already lah! Singapore is not operating at its full potential yet because we have a culture of being too cautious. I think we can be more creative and adventurous to take some risk. I hold the idea of fun very close to my heart. I want to encour</title>
    <updated>2023-08-25T02:02:30+00:00</updated>
    <content>Too Kiasi already lah! Singapore is not operating at its full potential yet because we have a culture of being too cautious. I think we can be more creative and adventurous to take some risk. I hold the idea of fun very close to my heart. I want to encourage fun ways for our youths to educate themselves! This will ultimately help us be more competitive and prosperous.#ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271074452161482002" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-25T02:02:30+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271123441485450514</id>
    <title>am standing as a true non-partisan Presidential candidate and I have never had any affiliation with political parties. I will be able to discharge my duties without fear or favour. I will be able to serve all Singaporeans in their best interests while wor</title>
    <updated>2023-08-25T05:12:36+00:00</updated>
    <content>am standing as a true non-partisan Presidential candidate and I have never had any affiliation with political parties. I will be able to discharge my duties without fear or favour. I will be able to serve all Singaporeans in their best interests while working with the government. The people of Singapore needs someone who is familiar with the machinery of the government yet is non-partisan. I am that person. #unitedforourfuture #ngkoksong2023  🖐🏽❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271123441485450514" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-25T05:12:36+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271151362652523783</id>
    <title>I was given the opportunity to share with the leaders of Taman Bacaan my gratitude to the Malay and Muslim communities for the backing of Salleh, Ameer, Hamid as my assenters. Taman Bacaan and I had also talked about the idea of building more interracial </title>
    <updated>2023-08-25T07:00:56+00:00</updated>
    <content>I was given the opportunity to share with the leaders of Taman Bacaan my gratitude to the Malay and Muslim communities for the backing of Salleh, Ameer, Hamid as my assenters. Taman Bacaan and I had also talked about the idea of building more interracial help so that we can all be more invested in each other's communities and that is crucial for our long-term stability. They also talked about the deep kindness they want to see in Singapore. I felt the force of it. Thank you, Taman Bacaan! #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏽❤️ Vote for Me </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271151362652523783" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-25T07:00:56+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271184150768438536</id>
    <title>After an exciting interview today, I came back to rest before bringing Max for his daily walk. He looks forward to these walks and it is our special family time together. I’ll be headed out again soon to Kent Ridge Guild House for ‘Meet The Presidential C</title>
    <updated>2023-08-25T09:08:10+00:00</updated>
    <content>After an exciting interview today, I came back to rest before bringing Max for his daily walk. He looks forward to these walks and it is our special family time together. I’ll be headed out again soon to Kent Ridge Guild House for ‘Meet The Presidential Candidate Series’ hosted by Prof Walid! Many of you have asked me if this will be live-streamed. It won’t be but I will be sharing some of the insights on social media this week. I am excited to meet more amazing Singaporeans soon! #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture #catsoftiktok #cats #britishshorthaircat  🖐🏽❤️ Vote for Me </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271184150768438536" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-25T09:08:10+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
