<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial</id>
  <title>ngkoksongofficial TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-30T13:03:40+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/ngkoksongofficial.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from ngkoksongofficial</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272665870663535890</id>
    <title>The value of our reserves is strategically important and must be kept a secret. It is dangerous to suggest that the Government should reveal this information publicly, which would only benefit our enemies. This goes against our national interest and leave</title>
    <updated>2023-08-29T08:57:59+00:00</updated>
    <content>The value of our reserves is strategically important and must be kept a secret. It is dangerous to suggest that the Government should reveal this information publicly, which would only benefit our enemies. This goes against our national interest and leave the Singapore Dollar vulnerable to attack or manipulation.  If elected President, I will want to know how much we have in the reserves, what proportion is set aside for future generations and how much is to be used to benefit the current generation. But I will keep our secrets safe. With my years of experience in the GIC building up our reserves, I will ask the right questions and work with the Government to ensure they are used prudently. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  Vote For Me  🖐🏼❤️</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272665870663535890" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-29T08:57:59+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272764869018012946</id>
    <title>I want to be the chief volunteer to rally more people to share their time and energy to serve the community. The next step is for Singaporeans to practise more inter-faith and inter-racial mutual help. We must go beyond just helping our own communities. T</title>
    <updated>2023-08-29T15:22:08+00:00</updated>
    <content>I want to be the chief volunteer to rally more people to share their time and energy to serve the community. The next step is for Singaporeans to practise more inter-faith and inter-racial mutual help. We must go beyond just helping our own communities. This will help us deepen our understanding of who we are as Singaporeans and find commonality in our Singaporean-ness. I have been practising philanthropy for a long time. I want to leverage on the connections I have to encourage people to come forward and foster volunteerism within institutions. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  Vote For Me  🖐🏼❤️</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272764869018012946" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-29T15:22:08+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272770463695179015</id>
    <title>If I win the election and have the honour to be your President, I will divest my stake in my company, Avanda Investment Management. It will be a big financial sacrifice because it is a profitable company, but I do not want there to be any perceived confli</title>
    <updated>2023-08-29T15:43:51+00:00</updated>
    <content>If I win the election and have the honour to be your President, I will divest my stake in my company, Avanda Investment Management. It will be a big financial sacrifice because it is a profitable company, but I do not want there to be any perceived conflict of interest. I’m answering a higher calling because money is not my goal in life. I want to serve the people of Singapore. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  Vote For Me  🖐🏼❤️</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272770463695179015" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-29T15:43:51+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272779133875260679</id>
    <title>This morning, I paid a visit to several coffee shops in Marine Parade and the nearby GoodLife! Makan community kitchen run by Montfort Care for seniors who live alone. It was good to see seniors of all walks of life and from different communities coming t</title>
    <updated>2023-08-29T16:17:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>This morning, I paid a visit to several coffee shops in Marine Parade and the nearby GoodLife! Makan community kitchen run by Montfort Care for seniors who live alone. It was good to see seniors of all walks of life and from different communities coming together for meals and companionship. This is an excellent example of how we can go beyond self-help to inter-racial, inter-faith mutual help. If I am elected, I will use my platform to foster more of such initiatives. In the afternoon, I returned to Mediacorp to record my second Presidential Candidate Broadcast which will air tomorrow. It will be one of the final messages that will go out before Cooling-Off Day so I wanted to get it right. Then in the evening, I had planned to visit Clementi 448 Market &amp; Food Centre, but unfortunately did not get a chance to. I spent almost an hour meeting and taking photos with residents who had formed an orderly queue near the mall. It was a warm and happy occasion, marred only by a heckler who approached my team and me with hostility. I won't speculate on the young man's motives. He must have had his frustrations, which he chose to take out on me for reasons only known to himself. I bear him no ill will. I had earlier spoken to the media about my worries regarding a growing cynicism and distrust towards the government among the youth of today. If elected, I will do all I can to inspire more hope among Singaporeans, including those who do not support me.  We all face difficulties in life. Let's all be more understanding towards one another. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  Vote For Me  🖐🏼❤️</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272779133875260679" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-29T16:17:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272943587954920722</id>
    <title>My campaign efforts were focused online and on the ground. Through my social media efforts, I was able to interact with and understand our youths, including their fears and hopes. Similarly, walking the ground has been very heartening. Nothing beats heari</title>
    <updated>2023-08-30T02:55:42+00:00</updated>
    <content>My campaign efforts were focused online and on the ground. Through my social media efforts, I was able to interact with and understand our youths, including their fears and hopes. Similarly, walking the ground has been very heartening. Nothing beats hearing the concerns and stories of Singaporeans first hand. They have helped me level the playing field with other candidates. I have been very candid and direct with you because I want you to know that I will keep to my word. Thank you for trusting me and giving me your time and attention. If elected President, I will carry out my duties honourably.🖐🏼❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272943587954920722" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-30T02:55:42+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7273038601250721031</id>
    <title>I strongly believe that the time has come for the elected president to be non-partisan. We may have our differences of views and political affiliations, but differences must not become divisions in our society. We must stay united for the future. #ngkokso</title>
    <updated>2023-08-30T09:04:22+00:00</updated>
    <content>I strongly believe that the time has come for the elected president to be non-partisan. We may have our differences of views and political affiliations, but differences must not become divisions in our society. We must stay united for the future. #ngkoksong2023 #ngkoksong2023  ❤️🖐🏼 Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7273038601250721031" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-30T09:04:22+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7273068422915738898</id>
    <title>On the final day of the campaign, I paid a visit to Hougang Hainanese Village in the morning. I grew up in Hougang and it always brings back fond memories. I was glad to be able to make a stop at this nostalgic place. I was blessed to be able to visit Foo</title>
    <updated>2023-08-30T11:00:05+00:00</updated>
    <content>On the final day of the campaign, I paid a visit to Hougang Hainanese Village in the morning. I grew up in Hougang and it always brings back fond memories. I was glad to be able to make a stop at this nostalgic place. I was blessed to be able to visit Foo Hai Ch'an Monastery, hosted by Reverend Ming Yi. We discussed the benefits of meditation and the importance of inter faith and inter-racial collaboration. I presented a book entitled Common Ground to the Reverend, which commemorates a two-day event I organised in 2012 to bring together leaders from different faiths to find common ground in the practice of meditation. I also had the privilege of meditating together with the devotees in silence. I then made a stop at the Church of the Holy Family to say a short prayer. My church holds a special place in my heart. It is where I worship with my family. It is where I said goodbye to my late wife Patricia and delivered her eulogy. My final stop of the campaign is at Kopitam Square in Sengkang. One last chance to meet my fellow Singaporeans before Cooling-Off Day. I have given my very best for this contest. Thank you to each and every voter who plans to support me on Friday. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐️❤️ Vote for Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7273068422915738898" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-30T11:00:05+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7273088478001253650</id>
    <title>I started my campaign at Kangkar, where I was born. I have ended it in Sengkang, near where I grew up.  This homecoming is my way of remembering my roots and expressing gratitude to the place I came from and the people who shaped me into who I am. I'm rea</title>
    <updated>2023-08-30T12:17:55+00:00</updated>
    <content>I started my campaign at Kangkar, where I was born. I have ended it in Sengkang, near where I grew up.  This homecoming is my way of remembering my roots and expressing gratitude to the place I came from and the people who shaped me into who I am. I'm ready to serve Singapore and Singaporeans. Please vote for me. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote for Me </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7273088478001253650" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-30T12:17:55+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7273092346340723976</id>
    <title>It’s been fun! Thank you Singapore 🇸🇬 Vote for me 🖐🏾❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </title>
    <updated>2023-08-30T12:32:55+00:00</updated>
    <content>It’s been fun! Thank you Singapore 🇸🇬 Vote for me 🖐🏾❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7273092346340723976" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-30T12:32:55+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7273100263978798343</id>
    <title>I would be humbled to be your president. Thank you for your trust in me. This is the greatest honour of my life. 🖐🏾❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </title>
    <updated>2023-08-30T13:03:40+00:00</updated>
    <content>I would be humbled to be your president. Thank you for your trust in me. This is the greatest honour of my life. 🖐🏾❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7273100263978798343" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-30T13:03:40+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
