<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial</id>
  <title>ngkoksongofficial TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-28T12:19:17+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/ngkoksongofficial.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from ngkoksongofficial</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271881750270233864</id>
    <title>Love is the greatest experience we can have in our lives. One of my fondest memories was the day I fell in love with my wife, Patricia, in school. We went on to share 33 years of love during our marriage. We stood by each other through thick and thin, esp</title>
    <updated>2023-08-27T06:15:15+00:00</updated>
    <content>Love is the greatest experience we can have in our lives. One of my fondest memories was the day I fell in love with my wife, Patricia, in school. We went on to share 33 years of love during our marriage. We stood by each other through thick and thin, especially during the bad times. When she was diagnosed with cancer, I took a year off from work to spend as much time as I could with her. Towards her last few days, she thanked me for loving her because she said it had helped her overcome her fear of death.  I had to take responsibility for her and my kids, as a single dad, after she passed. I had to step up. Now, I want to be responsible for the people of Singapore by standing to be the President. I love my country for all that it has provided me and my family. I want to inspire others to never lose hope too. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote for Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271881750270233864" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-27T06:15:15+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271894098217422088</id>
    <title>As President, I want to bring businesses together to do philanthropy. I want to promote the idea of sharing, not giving. When you are able to give and care, it makes you a kinder person and fills you with joy. You’re benefiting as much as the receiver.  I</title>
    <updated>2023-08-27T07:03:09+00:00</updated>
    <content>As President, I want to bring businesses together to do philanthropy. I want to promote the idea of sharing, not giving. When you are able to give and care, it makes you a kinder person and fills you with joy. You’re benefiting as much as the receiver.  I am determined to foster this culture of giving time and resources to the less fortunate. This might include the migrant workers, the poor and the dying. We should consider structuring volunteerism within companies and organisations. We must remember to be a gracious society ❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote for Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271894098217422088" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-27T07:03:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271915714414447880</id>
    <title>It is critical that we honour the spirit of the Constitution. The President is a unifying figure. He or she should not be beholden to any political parties. I stand as a truly independent candidate with a heart-powered team. I am not backed by any parties</title>
    <updated>2023-08-27T08:27:02+00:00</updated>
    <content>It is critical that we honour the spirit of the Constitution. The President is a unifying figure. He or she should not be beholden to any political parties. I stand as a truly independent candidate with a heart-powered team. I am not backed by any parties, but rather by my record of serving the people of Singapore.  I am driven by love from my family and the people I have met over my life, including the past few weeks. I will safeguard our national treasures based on the best interest of the people. In times of political or other crises, I will make the most objective judgment call. Thank you for standing with me. We stand United for our future. 🖐🏼❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271915714414447880" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-27T08:27:02+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271941267670568200</id>
    <title>We must not allow this Presidential Election to become a proxy fight between the government endorsed candidate and the opposition endorsed candidate. This is dangerous and divisive. Save the party politics for the next General Election and do not let it p</title>
    <updated>2023-08-27T10:06:11+00:00</updated>
    <content>We must not allow this Presidential Election to become a proxy fight between the government endorsed candidate and the opposition endorsed candidate. This is dangerous and divisive. Save the party politics for the next General Election and do not let it pollute the office of the President, which is supposed to be a unifying force. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271941267670568200" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-27T10:06:11+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271983392982453512</id>
    <title>Statement by Salleh Marican on the need for the President to be non-partisan. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture 🖐🏼❤️. </title>
    <updated>2023-08-27T12:49:39+00:00</updated>
    <content>Statement by Salleh Marican on the need for the President to be non-partisan. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture 🖐🏼❤️. </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7271983392982453512" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-27T12:49:39+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272036493357534471</id>
    <title>Never a dull day during campaign season! At Tampines Round Market in the morning, I spoke about the importance of ensuring the Elected President is not beholden to any political party. We cannot have a President who may be manipulated to serve the politic</title>
    <updated>2023-08-27T16:15:42+00:00</updated>
    <content>Never a dull day during campaign season! At Tampines Round Market in the morning, I spoke about the importance of ensuring the Elected President is not beholden to any political party. We cannot have a President who may be manipulated to serve the political agenda of any party. By the time I got to Chinatown Complex around lunchtime, news had broken that another opposition party leader had endorsed one of the other candidates. Naturally, the media had many questions for me about this development. I shared my views frankly. Let's not mince words. The move by some members of opposition parties to endorse a certain candidate is dangerous and divisive. Turning the Presidential Election into a proxy for a General Election is a polarising move that aims to force Singaporeans to choose between a government-endorsed candidate and an opposition-endorsed candidate. I am glad that not all opposition parties have decided to do this. Responsible opposition politicians understand the difference between a PE and a GE. They know how important it is to ensure the President remains a unifying force in Singapore and not an office to be used as a backdoor to pressure the Government on policy matters. I was very happy to receive such a warm welcome from Singaporeans at both hawker centres. Many, many people came to say hello, including some who are still too young to vote but have been following the developments closely. Wonderful to see such political awareness among the future electorate. In the evening, I had a more lighthearted session with @Hao on a TikTok livestream where he invited his followers and friends to Ask Me Anything or AMA! We talked about a wide range of topics, including how to deal with personal conflicts, managing one's finances and why the President cannot lower the GST rate. Another AMA video which I had filmed together with Tharman also premiered on Straits Times. We both fielded questions on everything from mental health among youth to how we would celebrate if we won the election. Just a few days left before we go to the polls. I'm going all out to meet as many Singaporeans as I can.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272036493357534471" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-27T16:15:42+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272264036132130056</id>
    <title>I’ve always been serious when it comes to discharging my duties. At the same time, I am a very lighthearted person. In my 45 years of public service, I took my job of protecting our reserves seriously because I found joy in contributing to our growth. It </title>
    <updated>2023-08-28T06:58:39+00:00</updated>
    <content>I’ve always been serious when it comes to discharging my duties. At the same time, I am a very lighthearted person. In my 45 years of public service, I took my job of protecting our reserves seriously because I found joy in contributing to our growth. It was never a burden.  The past few weeks have been amazing. Meeting all of you has given me so much joy and I want to be seen as your friend in the Istana. But I will not give in to fear or favour when it comes to safeguarding our treasures. The president must ultimately have the competence and expertise to be the head of state.#ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272264036132130056" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-28T06:58:39+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272310875845840146</id>
    <title>I am not a yes-man. In my 45 years of public service, I had plenty of experience standing my ground to do what was right, even if that meant disagreeing with people I reported to. If I am elected as your President, I will not hesitate to object to decisio</title>
    <updated>2023-08-28T10:00:25+00:00</updated>
    <content>I am not a yes-man. In my 45 years of public service, I had plenty of experience standing my ground to do what was right, even if that meant disagreeing with people I reported to. If I am elected as your President, I will not hesitate to object to decisions that are against the interests of the people of Singapore. I know how to work with the Government, for the people of Singapore, without being disruptive. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272310875845840146" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-28T10:00:25+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272328184421567752</id>
    <title>Dear Singaporeans, we must not get confused between the Presidential Election and the General Election. Members of some opposition parties have banded together to show their support for one of the other candidates. Another candidate is endorsed by the gov</title>
    <updated>2023-08-28T11:07:35+00:00</updated>
    <content>Dear Singaporeans, we must not get confused between the Presidential Election and the General Election. Members of some opposition parties have banded together to show their support for one of the other candidates. Another candidate is endorsed by the governing party. We must not let them turn this into a proxy fight between the Government and the opposition. This election is not about that. It is about all the people of Singapore, regardless of political affiliations.  The President must be a unifying force, not another source of division and discord. Those who wish to fight it out in the political arena should wait for the next GE. Stand united with me in solidarity to uphold the integrity and honour of the President’s office. 🖐🏼❤️ #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272328184421567752" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-28T11:07:35+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272346659336555794</id>
    <title>I will not stand for politicians making a mockery out of our Presidency. Since independence, Singapore has been recognised internationally for its exceptional political and social stability. Our founding leaders and our past generations have worked hard i</title>
    <updated>2023-08-28T12:19:17+00:00</updated>
    <content>I will not stand for politicians making a mockery out of our Presidency. Since independence, Singapore has been recognised internationally for its exceptional political and social stability. Our founding leaders and our past generations have worked hard in unity to lift us out of poverty into a first-world country. It is critical now, more than ever, that our head of state is able to navigate Singapore through crises. The office must be respected and honoured. I stand as a non partisan candidate, not beholden to anyone. I will not be pressured by partisan interests. I want to serve the people of Singapore honourably. #ngkoksong2023 #unitedforourfuture  🖐🏼❤️ Vote For Me</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@ngkoksongofficial/video/7272346659336555794" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-28T12:19:17+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
