<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg</id>
  <title>tharman.sg TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-11-20T05:12:59+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/tharman.sg.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://fnbrg.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from tharman.sg</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg/video/7283817481972534529</id>
    <title>The Community Chest Uniting Hearts Charity TV show last Sunday saw an outpouring of support, with over 20,000 contributions. Community Chest supports over 200 social programmes, helping everyone have hope.</title>
    <updated>2023-09-28T10:11:59+00:00</updated>
    <content>The Community Chest Uniting Hearts Charity TV show last Sunday saw an outpouring of support, with over 20,000 contributions. Community Chest supports over 200 social programmes, helping everyone have hope.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg/video/7283817481972534529" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-28T10:11:59+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg/video/7287073623624486145</id>
    <title>Volunteers are a blessing.  @Singapore Red Cross promotes something essential, that we must strengthen in national character: solidarity with those facing disadvantage, within and beyond our shores.  #sgredcross #TogetherForHumanity #RespectforAll ‎</title>
    <updated>2023-10-07T04:47:28+00:00</updated>
    <content>Volunteers are a blessing.  @Singapore Red Cross promotes something essential, that we must strengthen in national character: solidarity with those facing disadvantage, within and beyond our shores.  #sgredcross #TogetherForHumanity #RespectforAll ‎</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg/video/7287073623624486145" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-07T04:47:28+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg/video/7290047065906826503</id>
    <title>I was happy to cheer on our Lions in the National Stadium on Thursday when they played against Guam in the Asian Qualifiers for the FIFA World Cup 2026.   First, the positives. The Lions won 2-1 -  thanks to two superbly taken goals by Christopher van Hui</title>
    <updated>2023-10-15T05:05:54+00:00</updated>
    <content>I was happy to cheer on our Lions in the National Stadium on Thursday when they played against Guam in the Asian Qualifiers for the FIFA World Cup 2026.   First, the positives. The Lions won 2-1 -  thanks to two superbly taken goals by Christopher van Huizen and Jacob Mahler. And we had over 10,000 roaring fans in the stadium.    But 2-1 in this home leg is not a strong score to be taking into the away leg in Guam. The Lions did well to dominate the game, but were unlucky with chances right in front of the goal.   This is a knock-out round, for teams that are lower in FIFA’s ranking (Singapore is 157th and Guam 201st). Let’s hope we hold that lead next Tuesday in Guam. The Lions are showing spirit, and good team-play, and can do it.   If we make it to the next round, it will be tough competition – with South Korea, China and Thailand in the Group. But valuable exposure. Video footage of handshake with the players, credits to Mediacorp</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg/video/7290047065906826503" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-15T05:05:54+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg/video/7292738785421397256</id>
    <title>Happy to join some of the performers yesterday at a rehearsal for tonight’s  President's Star Charity.  The show is not just a collection of performances. They are stories that reflect our deepest values, and build on each other.  This year's President's </title>
    <updated>2023-10-22T11:11:09+00:00</updated>
    <content>Happy to join some of the performers yesterday at a rehearsal for tonight’s  President's Star Charity.  The show is not just a collection of performances. They are stories that reflect our deepest values, and build on each other.  This year's President's Star Charity reminds us that respect for the dignity of every individual is the key to building a fairer, better and more inclusive society. Hope you catch the show at 7.30pm on mewatch (link below) and Channel 5.  https://www.mewatch.sg/ #RespectForAll #PresidentsStarCharity</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg/video/7292738785421397256" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-22T11:11:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg/video/7294922430982671634</id>
    <title>“Never let go of your smile, for it seems to melt everyone’s heart in a minute to a mile. Never let go of the courage and strength I know you have kept hidden within” - from Stephanie Esther Fam’s poem ‘Never Let Go’. We can all learn something from Steph</title>
    <updated>2023-10-28T08:25:11+00:00</updated>
    <content>“Never let go of your smile, for it seems to melt everyone’s heart in a minute to a mile. Never let go of the courage and strength I know you have kept hidden within” - from Stephanie Esther Fam’s poem ‘Never Let Go’. We can all learn something from Stephanie’s bravery and unyielding spirit. Watch her here. Born with cerebral palsy, she has not let it limit her. She wrote her first book of poetry, “Shades”, over 18 years, and is a leading practitioner in disability-led theatre. My wife and I had the privilege of joining Stephanie to read ‘Never Let Go’ at the President’s Star Charity show. We were accompanied by dancers who themselves inspired with their resilience, June Lin and Weng Jiaying from Diverse Abilities Dance Collective (DADC). Together with Shahrin Johry and Shahizam Sulaiman from Maya Dance Group, violinist Dania Munira and pianist Isa Dahlan from the Orkestra Melayu Singapura, and Zoe Tay and Qli Quek on steel tongue drums. The President’s Star Charity supports efforts to uplift everyone. Never let go of our belief in the strength and goodness in each person. #RespectForAll #PresidentsStarCharity Video by Mediacorp</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg/video/7294922430982671634" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-28T08:25:11+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg/video/7295680520648789249</id>
    <title>I was happy to receive Prime Minister Dato’ Seri Anwar Ibrahim at the Istana this morning. PM Anwar is visiting Singapore for the 10th Singapore-Malaysia Leaders’ Retreat. We share much in common – culture, kinship, and history. And regular contacts and e</title>
    <updated>2023-10-30T09:26:38+00:00</updated>
    <content>I was happy to receive Prime Minister Dato’ Seri Anwar Ibrahim at the Istana this morning. PM Anwar is visiting Singapore for the 10th Singapore-Malaysia Leaders’ Retreat. We share much in common – culture, kinship, and history. And regular contacts and exchanges between our leaders, civil servants and entrepreneurs. Singapore is a major investor in Malaysia, and our peoples cross the border often when we have breaks, to enjoy each other’s tourist attractions. These shared bonds have allowed us to weather challenges together in the past. They will also enable us to work together to create a more borderless environment for enterprises, local and foreign, so we can complement each other and maximise the economic potential of our countries as well as ASEAN. Singapore and Malaysia are working together on several important initiatives that will benefit both our peoples, including the Johor-Singapore Special Economic Zone and in renewable energy. PM Anwar and I also exchanged views on global and regional developments. We expressed our commitment to strengthen our cooperation both bilaterally and through ASEAN to overcome shared challenges and invest in the opportunities of the future. I wished PM Anwar a fruitful visit in Singapore, and look forward to seeing him again before long.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg/video/7295680520648789249" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-30T09:26:38+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg/video/7298307485553675522</id>
    <title>It was a pleasure for me to receive HRH Prince William at the Istana today. Prince William is in Singapore for the finals of The Earthshot Prize, a global initiative he launched in 2020 to promote ground-breaking solutions to the world’s largest environme</title>
    <updated>2023-11-06T11:20:34+00:00</updated>
    <content>It was a pleasure for me to receive HRH Prince William at the Istana today. Prince William is in Singapore for the finals of The Earthshot Prize, a global initiative he launched in 2020 to promote ground-breaking solutions to the world’s largest environmental challenges. The 15 finalists for #EarthshotPrize come from 6 continents, and made it through from over 1,100 nominations. They tackle big problems. From using seaweed-based feed for cows to dramatically reduce the methane emitted into the atmosphere when they burp, to creating sustainable dyes that reduce the fashion industry’s excessive use of water and harmful chemicals. Prince William and I discussed the innovative solutions needed to hold back climate change and a worsening global water crisis. And the optimism that can and must be created by discovering and implementing them on a global scale. Singapore and the UK are stepping up our collaboration in this critical task as part of the Strategic Partnership that PM Lee and PM Sunak launched two months ago.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg/video/7298307485553675522" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-06T11:20:34+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg/video/7300797010058300674</id>
    <title>Enthralling performance by House of Music - yIN Harmony. #Deepavali #IstanaOpenHouse</title>
    <updated>2023-11-13T04:21:15+00:00</updated>
    <content>Enthralling performance by House of Music - yIN Harmony. #Deepavali #IstanaOpenHouse</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg/video/7300797010058300674" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-13T04:21:15+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg/video/7300926832579316993</id>
    <title>Deepavali Istana Open House 2023</title>
    <updated>2023-11-13T12:45:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Deepavali Istana Open House 2023</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg/video/7300926832579316993" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-13T12:45:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg/video/7303407958249983240</id>
    <title>We must develop and use our emotional intelligence or EQ, through life. It will matter even more in a future of AI.  #RespectForAll #SFF2023  Video footage credits to: Singapore FinTech Festival </title>
    <updated>2023-11-20T05:12:59+00:00</updated>
    <content>We must develop and use our emotional intelligence or EQ, through life. It will matter even more in a future of AI.  #RespectForAll #SFF2023  Video footage credits to: Singapore FinTech Festival </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@tharman.sg/video/7303407958249983240" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-20T05:12:59+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
